<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<dictionary>
  <locale name="en">
    <message key="quest1Title">Installing a Fountain</message>
    <message key="quest1Comment">Thanks for your help. This fountain looks impressive! I can't wait to show my friends!</message>
    <message key="quest2Title">Makeover</message>
    <message key="quest2Comment">You look great in those new clothes!
The shops here have all the coolest clothes!</message>
    <message key="quest3Title">The First Order</message>
    <message key="quest3Comment">You can order various treats at the Cafe or at the Club which will restore your energy.</message>
    <message key="quest4Title">Hit the Dance Floor!</message>
    <message key="quest4Comment">Here, enjoy this refreshing drink and restore your energy with it.</message>
    <message key="quest5Title">Tutorial</message>
    <message key="quest5Comment">You don't have a lot of furniture yet, so here are a few pieces to start with.</message>
    <message key="quest6Title">The Sweet Life</message>
    <message key="quest6Description">Why don't you walk to the nearest Cafe and buy a tasty treat? It will help you to recover your strength and unwind.</message>
    <message key="quest6Task1Title">Go to the Cafe and eat a slice of pie or a pizza with a cup of coffee</message>
    <message key="quest6Comment">Hint: To get to the Cafe or the Club, click on Places in the lower part of the screen.</message>
    <message key="quest9Title">In Search of Buddies</message>
    <message key="quest9Description">Now that your apartment is looking good, it's time to make new buddies. After all, they make life interesting.</message>
    <message key="quest9Comment">Hint: Click on one of the players, select Relationship from the list and click Meet.</message>
    <message key="quest10Title">Neighborly Help</message>
    <message key="quest10Description">Friendly neighbors always help one another. You can help your neighbors by cleaning up their apartments and earn silver coins in the process!</message>
    <message key="quest11Title">Feel Cramped? Time to Expand!</message>
    <message key="quest11Description">Feeling cramped living in just one room? Now you can afford to buy another room and furnish it.</message>
    <message key="quest12Title">Street Laws</message>
    <message key="quest12Description">Keeping the street clean is important. If you take it upon yourself to clean up a little every day you'll earn yourself the residents' gratitude and additional silver coins.</message>
    <message key="quest13Title">Trio</message>
    <message key="quest13Description">Two rooms is good, but three is even better! Here is your chance to buy another room. Additional living space is more than mere convenience - just think of the parties you can throw!</message>
    <message key="quest14Title">Generous Gesture</message>
    <message key="quest14Description">There's an awesome party at the Club. A good opportunity to make some new friends.</message>
    <message key="quest15Title">An Inexperienced Gardener</message>
    <message key="quest15Description">A lovely garden recently opened in Avataria. You should get a job there looking after the plants! A job is great way to make extra silver.</message>
    <message key="quest16Title">First Renovations</message>
    <message key="quest16Description">It's time to renovate! Let's start with one of the rooms.</message>
    <message key="quest16Task1Title">Put up wallpaper</message>
    <message key="quest16Task2Title">Lay floors</message>
    <message key="quest17Title">My Home Is My Castle</message>
    <message key="quest17Description">A new door will not only look good, it protects your belongings from uninvited guests.</message>
    <message key="quest17Task1Title">Buy a new door</message>
    <message key="quest17Task2Title">Install the door in the apartment</message>
    <message key="quest18Title">Live it Up!</message>
    <message key="quest18Description">This night is yours! Show off your moves on the dance floor!</message>
    <message key="quest19Title">On the Wings of Love</message>
    <message key="quest19Description">Love is a beautiful thing. No matter the season, there are loving couples everywhere you look. Maybe you should think about finding your soul mate?</message>
    <message key="quest20Title">Let's Trade!</message>
    <message key="quest20Description">One of your friends saw you wearing something fashionable and has asked you to borrow it. Why don't you trade it for something else?</message>
    <message key="quest20Task1Title">Trade something with a friend</message>
    <message key="quest22Title">Novice Florist</message>
    <message key="quest22Description">Your work hasn't gone unnoticed; more and more people have been coming to marvel at this wondrous garden. But your work is also far from over.</message>
    <message key="quest23Title">Helping Hand</message>
    <message key="quest23Description">Lend a helping hand and get the same in return! Today you'll help your neighbors clean up, and tomorrow they'll return the favor.</message>
    <message key="quest26Title">Amateur Horticulturist</message>
    <message key="quest26Description">I see you like working in the garden. After all, what could be better than a hobby that you enjoy and that earns a bit of cash?</message>
    <message key="quest27Title">Dance Marathon</message>
    <message key="quest27Description">This is a real dance marathon. Show everyone you're more than just a pretty face, but a real star on the dance floor!</message>
    <message key="quest28Title">Love Is in the Air</message>
    <message key="quest28Description">Some say a kiss is just a kiss, but when you meet someone special, a kiss can mean so much more.</message>
    <message key="quest29Title">My Bathroom</message>
    <message key="quest29Description">Good hygiene is the foundation of good health! And how can you have good hygiene without a morning shower? You need a bathroom!</message>
    <message key="quest29Task1Title">Install a bath</message>
    <message key="quest29Task2Title">Install a sink</message>
    <message key="quest29Task3Title">Install a toilet</message>
    <message key="quest29Task4Title">Hang a mirror</message>
    <message key="quest30Title">Out With the Old</message>
    <message key="quest30Description">Soon your wardrobe will be full of new clothes, which means you can easily get rid of the old garments. Selling them isn't very lucrative, but at least you'll free up lots of space.</message>
    <message key="quest30Task1Title">Sell some clothes</message>
    <message key="quest30Comment">Hint: To sell an item, open your Inventory and click on Sell below one of the items.</message>
    <message key="quest31Title">Your New Image</message>
    <message key="quest31Description">Do you want new opportunities? Do you want to mingle with the most popular people, wear the coolest clothes and always be in the spotlight? Then you need to start thinking about your image.</message>
    <message key="quest31Comment">Hint: Accumulate 60 image points by buying new items in the clothing store.</message>
    <message key="quest32Title">Place the bed</message>
    <message key="quest32Description">Sleeping on the sofa is getting old, isn't it? Now you can afford to roll around in a big comfortable bed.</message>
    <message key="quest32Task1Title">Buy a bed</message>
    <message key="quest32Task2Title">Place a bed in the apartment</message>
    <message key="quest33Title">Fresh and Full of Strength</message>
    <message key="quest33Description">You always want to do more, but for that you need lots of strength and energy.</message>
    <message key="quest34Title">A New Level of Comfort</message>
    <message key="quest34Description">People always want to get better things, particularly in the comfort of home. After all, home is where you feel cozy and protected.</message>
    <message key="quest35Title">Try Your Luck!</message>
    <message key="quest35Description">Feeling lucky? Go ahead, spin Fortune's Wheel!</message>
    <message key="quest36Title">A Change of Image</message>
    <message key="quest36Description">It's time to change your look. New levels, new achievements, and plenty of crazy parties await you! Not to mention, new acquaintances and a storm of new emotions!</message>
    <message key="quest37Title">Fighting for Cleanliness</message>
    <message key="quest37Description">The street requires constant looking after. And it's up to you to keep it clean. All of the residents have to do their part.</message>
    <message key="quest38Title">Wild Shopping</message>
    <message key="quest38Description">It's time to freshen up your wardrobe. Hurry up to the store before everything's gone!</message>
    <message key="quest38Task1Title">Buy a pair of shoes</message>
    <message key="quest38Task2Title">Buy pants or shorts</message>
    <message key="quest38Task3Title">Buy a shirt or a t-shirt</message>
    <message key="quest38Task4Title">Buy a coat</message>
    <message key="quest39Task2Title">Buy pants or a skirt</message>
    <message key="quest39Task3Title">Buy a shirt</message>
    <message key="quest40Title">Foamy Symphony</message>
    <message key="quest40Description">Just a few accessories can transform your bathroom, making it much more luxurious.</message>
    <message key="quest40Task1Title">Place 3 accessories in the bathroom</message>
    <message key="quest40Task2Title">Place a cabinet in the bathroom</message>
    <message key="quest41Title">Beginner's Luck!</message>
    <message key="quest41Description">You've already spun Fortune's Wheel, but this time you'll need to win several times to complete the task.</message>
    <message key="quest42Title">Life of Comfort</message>
    <message key="quest42Description">Your apartment is transforming before your very eyes. And not only yours, but all those around you as well. But you have much to do still to reach the next level of comfort. It's all up to you!</message>
    <message key="quest43Title">Keep it Up!</message>
    <message key="quest43Description">Big plans require lots of cash. But all that hard work really pays off when you see the results.</message>
    <message key="quest44Title">Interior</message>
    <message key="quest44Description">Go ahead and experiment with your apartment's interior. Everything you could possibly need is in the Furniture Store!</message>
    <message key="quest44Task1Title">Place a floor lamp</message>
    <message key="quest44Task2Title">Hang a wall lamp</message>
    <message key="quest44Task3Title">Place a vase</message>
    <message key="quest45Title">Beauty Is in the Details</message>
    <message key="quest45Description">You can find plenty of creative accessories in the Clothing Store. Take this opportunity to enhance your image!</message>
    <message key="quest45Task1Title">Buy any 3 accessories</message>
    <message key="quest46Title">Mutual Help</message>
    <message key="quest46Description">There's plenty of work to be done. And sometimes it feels like as soon as you clean up one area, another gets dirty! It's enough to make you wonder: where are your neighbors?</message>
    <message key="quest47Title">Image Is Everything!</message>
    <message key="quest47Description">You've worked hard on your image and you've achieved a lot. Still, there are new heights to conquer!</message>
    <message key="quest48Title">Piggy Bank</message>
    <message key="quest48Description">Money has a tendency of getting spent too quickly, so you'll need a piggy bank to start saving up. A three-liter jar works as well!</message>
    <message key="quest49Title">2 + 2 = 4</message>
    <message key="quest49Description">Everybody in the world knows that! And now you can afford to buy another room. One that's large, bright and spacious.</message>
    <message key="quest50Title">Kitchen Design</message>
    <message key="quest50Description">Now you have enough rooms to turn one into a kitchen. It's far more comfortable to eat at a kitchen table instead of on a sofa.</message>
    <message key="quest50Task1Title">Place 5 kitchen modules</message>
    <message key="quest50Task2Title">Place a kitchen table</message>
    <message key="quest50Task3Title">Place 2 kitchen chairs</message>
    <message key="quest51Title">Kitchen Decor</message>
    <message key="quest51Description">A few elegant accessories will make your kitchen unique. You can buy kitchen decor in the Furniture Store.</message>
    <message key="quest51Task1Title">Buy 3 decor elements for the kitchen</message>
    <message key="quest52Title">Away with Dirt!</message>
    <message key="quest52Description">After yesterday's heavy rains and near-hurricane winds, our street is a huge mess. You've got your work cut out for you.</message>
    <message key="quest53Title">Energizer</message>
    <message key="quest53Description">Where do you get the time and energy for everything? There's so much to be done and so little time to do it.</message>
    <message key="quest54Title">Lucky</message>
    <message key="quest54Description">Spin Fortune's Wheel and win! Don't miss this chance to earn a few hundred silver coins.</message>
    <message key="quest55Title">Peace and Comfort</message>
    <message key="quest55Description">Peace and comfort. Comfort and peace. How peaceful and how comfortable do you feel in your apartment?</message>
    <message key="quest57Title">King of Partying</message>
    <message key="quest57Description">So you think you can dance? Prove it!</message>
    <message key="quest58Title">Gardening Master</message>
    <message key="quest58Description">You accomplish any gardening task with ease. This is good, because work is piling up every day.</message>
    <message key="quest59Title">Help Is on the Way!</message>
    <message key="quest59Description">There's always work to be done in your neighbors' apartments. And the more neighbors you've got, the more work there is.</message>
    <message key="quest60Title">Change is for the Best</message>
    <message key="quest60Description">Time flows, things change, and everyone can see your success. Your image is now working for you. But you shouldn't take it easy now, either!</message>
    <message key="quest61Title">The Art of Seduction</message>
    <message key="quest61Description">If you think that you've already mastered the art of love, think again! There are still many secrets and mysteries to be revealed.</message>
    <message key="quest62Title">Cozy Is the Goal</message>
    <message key="quest62Description">The Furniture Store still has plenty to help make your apartment more cozy. Drop by when you get the chance and buy whatever catches your eye.</message>
    <message key="quest62Task1Title">Place a rug</message>
    <message key="quest62Task2Title">Place 2 armchairs</message>
    <message key="quest62Task3Title">Place a sofa</message>
    <message key="quest62Comment">Hint: You must place all the pieces of furniture in the same room to complete the task.</message>
    <message key="quest63Title">Interesting Associates</message>
    <message key="quest63Description">You never know where you'll meet new friends. Not that it matters. What matters is that a true friend will never abandon you, but will always be there for you in your time of need.</message>
    <message key="quest64Title">Rainy Day Savings</message>
    <message key="quest64Description">It may not be fashionable, but you can't argue against having some savings. It's a long way to the bank, but at home at least your money's all in one place.</message>
    <message key="quest65Title">Clean Streets</message>
    <message key="quest65Description">Every day you fight to keep the street clean, though you know tomorrow the fight will continue, same for the day after tomorrow, and the day after that. But, at least for today, the street will shine, and it's all thanks to you.</message>
    <message key="quest66Title">Perpetual Motor</message>
    <message key="quest66Description">When will the perpetual motion engine finally be invented? Or, even better, robots that do virtually all of the people's work for them? That's when we'll finally be able to do whatever our heart desires!</message>
    <message key="quest67Title">Golden Horseshoe</message>
    <message key="quest67Description">Let's see what Lady Luck has got in store for you today. Will you take the jackpot once again? Only time will tell.</message>
    <message key="quest68Title">A Cozy Nest</message>
    <message key="quest68Description">This is where you rest after a long day's work. And sometimes, when your routine becomes too much, it's where you throw wild parties. But no matter what happens, you come back here time after time. Because this is your home. Your cozy nest.</message>
    <message key="quest70Title">Home Sweet Home</message>
    <message key="quest70Description">You did it! Now you can afford to buy another room for your cozy apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest71Title">Replacing Doors</message>
    <message key="quest71Description">Aren't you tired of staring at these ugly doors connecting the rooms of your apartment? It's time to splurge and replace these doors with something more stylish.</message>
    <message key="quest71Task1Title">Buy 2 doors</message>
    <message key="quest71Task2Title">Replace doors in the apartment</message>
    <message key="quest71Comment">Hint: All doors must be installed in the main room to complete the task.</message>
    <message key="quest72Title">Installing Windows</message>
    <message key="quest72Description">Windows make the apartment more bright and pleasant to live in. What? You still don't have any windows? Don't worry, we can fix that.</message>
    <message key="quest72Task1Title">Buy 3 windows</message>
    <message key="quest72Task2Title">Install 3 windows in the apartment</message>
    <message key="quest72Comment">Hint: All 3 windows must be installed in the main room to complete the task.</message>
    <message key="quest73Title">Gardening Works</message>
    <message key="quest73Description">Today you were issued a big work order in the garden. But the payment will be worth it. Are you up to the challenge?</message>
    <message key="quest74Title">Spring Cleaning</message>
    <message key="quest74Description">It's spring cleaning in your building, which means you'll have to work hard to clean out the piled-up dirt and clutter.</message>
    <message key="quest75Title">High Society</message>
    <message key="quest75Description">Soon you'll gain access to the social elite. This is a great opportunity to get to know eccentric people and their friends. That can be intimidating, but trust me, it's worth it.</message>
    <message key="quest76Title">Bank in Your Pocket</message>
    <message key="quest76Description">While others are mindlessly spending their hard-earned cash, you're putting money away for a brighter future. A wise decision.</message>
    <message key="quest77Title">Dance Till You Drop</message>
    <message key="quest77Description">The most exclusive clubs have opened their doors to you. Do you have what it takes? The dance marathon has started!</message>
    <message key="quest78Title">Bliss</message>
    <message key="quest78Description">How lucky you are to be able relax in your very own bubbly Hot Tub. What, you don't have a Hot Tub? Get to the Furniture Store, quick!</message>
    <message key="quest78Task1Title">Buy a Hot Tub</message>
    <message key="quest78Task2Title">Install a Hot Tub in the apartment</message>
    <message key="quest79Title">Beach Season</message>
    <message key="quest79boyDescription">You're not going to go swimming in your regular clothes, are you? Or without clothes? This seasons Swimsuits are now available at the Clothing Store!</message>
    <message key="quest79girlDescription">You're not going to go swimming in your regular clothes, are you? Or without clothes? This seasons Swimsuits are now available at the Clothing Store!</message>
    <message key="quest79boyTask1Title">Buy swimming trunks</message>
    <message key="quest79girlTask1Title">Buy a swimsuit</message>
    <message key="quest80Title">Pirate Costume</message>
    <message key="quest80Description">Yo ho ho! If you want to feel like a pirate even for a minute, you'll need a pirate costume. And leave the rest to your imagination!</message>
    <message key="quest80boyTask1Title">Buy a pirate tricorne</message>
    <message key="quest80boyTask2Title">Buy a pirate eye patch</message>
    <message key="quest80boyTask3Title">Buy an earring</message>
    <message key="quest80boyTask4Title">Buy rolled-up trousers</message>
    <message key="quest80boyTask5Title">Buy a black coat with a zipper</message>
    <message key="quest80girlTask2Title">Buy black trousers</message>
    <message key="quest80girlTask3Title">Buy a black jacket</message>
    <message key="quest80girlTask4Title">Buy black varnished boots</message>
    <message key="quest80girlTask5Title">Buy a bikini top</message>
    <message key="quest81Title">Adding to Your Wardrobe</message>
    <message key="quest81Description">It's nice to have a wardrobe that allows you to wear different outfits for specific occasions. But you need to add to it occasionally.</message>
    <message key="quest81Task1Title">Buy new shoes</message>
    <message key="quest81Task2Title">Buy new pants and shorts</message>
    <message key="quest81Task3Title">Buy new shirts and t-shirts</message>
    <message key="quest81Task4Title">Buy new pants and skirts</message>
    <message key="quest81Task5Title">Buy new shirts</message>
    <message key="quest87Title">Life Happens</message>
    <message key="quest87Description">Life happens, so you shouldn't hide your emotions. And don't worry if someone doesn't understand you.</message>
    <message key="quest87Task1Title">Get angry while in the school</message>
    <message key="quest87Task2Title">Cry while in the park</message>
    <message key="quest87Comment">Hint: You can find the commands "get angry" and "cry" by clicking on your avatar.</message>
    <message key="quest88Title">Expressing Your Feelings</message>
    <message key="quest88Description">You can express your feelings and attitude toward other avatars in different ways. For this you have a whole arsenal of available emotions and actions. But remember, what you do may improve or harm your relationships with others.</message>
    <message key="quest89Title">Soak in a Hot Tub</message>
    <message key="quest89Description">Let's go for a nice soak in the Hot Tub!</message>
    <message key="quest89Task1Title">Relax in the Hot Tub</message>
    <message key="quest90Title">What's in a name?</message>
    <message key="quest90Description">You can change the names of your rooms whenever you want. Let's do that right now!</message>
    <message key="quest90Task1Title">Change a room's name</message>
    <message key="quest90Comment">Hint: To change the name of a room, click on the magnifying glass icon, then click Rename below one of the rooms.</message>
    <message key="quest91Title">Home Alone</message>
    <message key="quest91Description">Should you decide to spend some time in solitude, you can lock your apartment at any time and not allow anyone in.</message>
    <message key="quest91Task1Title">Lock the apartment to prevent visits</message>
    <message key="quest91Comment">Hint: To lock the apartment, click on the magnifying glass icon, then click on Lock Apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest92Title">Come on Over</message>
    <message key="quest92Description">Tired of feeling lonely? Bored sitting at home, all alone? Then unlock your apartment so that your friends can come visit!</message>
    <message key="quest92Task1Title">Unlock the apartment to allow visits</message>
    <message key="quest92Comment">Hint: To unlock the apartment, click on the magnifying glass icon, then click Unlock Apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest93Title">Clean up the Streets</message>
    <message key="quest93Description">Look at all the garbage in the street! I know you're tired, but it's every citizen's duty to help keep the streets clean.</message>
    <message key="quest94Title">For Cleanliness!</message>
    <message key="quest99Title">To the Last Weed</message>
    <message key="quest99Description">Ugh! The Garden is full of weeds! I know it's hard work, but it's every citizen's duty to contribute to a beautiful garden!</message>
    <message key="quest105Title">Best of the Best</message>
    <message key="quest105Description">You have a chance to distinguish yourself from the others and earn a reward for doing so. Do your best!</message>
    <message key="quest108Title">Master Gardener</message>
    <message key="quest108Description">Who handles gardening tasks best? Who wants to earn a bonus for good work?</message>
    <message key="quest111Title">The Well-Rested Worker</message>
    <message key="quest111Description">There is plenty of work in the garden, but make sure to rest well and regain your strength in between shifts.</message>
    <message key="quest112Title">Beauty and Comfort</message>
    <message key="quest112Description">To complete the task you must visit the Furniture Store, then work on decorating your apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest112Task2Title">Place 3 vases in a room</message>
    <message key="quest113Title">The Spinning Moment</message>
    <message key="quest113Description">It's time to see what luck tastes like! Spin Fortune's Wheel and see if luck smiles on you!</message>
    <message key="quest114Title">Meeting New People</message>
    <message key="quest114Description">It's time you met some new people, and there's no better place to do that in than the Club or the Cafe.</message>
    <message key="quest115Title">Rascal</message>
    <message key="quest115Description">Let's get into some trouble, eh?</message>
    <message key="quest116Title">Cleaning Up</message>
    <message key="quest116Description">Your neighbors need help again. Give them a hand?</message>
    <message key="quest117Title">Joys of Life</message>
    <message key="quest117Description">Work is done, so have some fun. It's time for you to relax and unwind.</message>
    <message key="quest118Title">Gardening Works</message>
    <message key="quest118Description">The local gardening association has given you new goals and tasks. Complete them for a nice reward.</message>
    <message key="quest119Title">Pursuing the Perfect Image</message>
    <message key="quest119Description">Fashion is constantly evolving and so does your image. It's people like you who define the trends!</message>
    <message key="quest120Title">The Chest</message>
    <message key="quest120Description">You've worked so hard! Time to treat yourself to some of the finer things in life!</message>
    <message key="quest121Title">Life Is a Dance</message>
    <message key="quest121Description">Dance wherever you feel like! Weather it's in the Club, in the Cafe or on the Streets, people can't help but join in!</message>
    <message key="quest133Title">Give Gifts!</message>
    <message key="quest133Description">It is better to give than receive. Here's your chance to show someone just how special they are to you!</message>
    <message key="quest134Title">Glassware</message>
    <message key="quest134Description">While cleaning the street, you can find lots of handy items that will be useful in your workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest135Title">Blissful Sweets</message>
    <message key="quest135Description">The Cafe attracts plenty of people. Some come here to chat over a cup of coffee, and others to participate in a pie throwing contests.</message>
    <message key="quest136Title">Lady Luck</message>
    <message key="quest136Description">Fortune's Wheel is a chance to win big money with very little effort. All it takes is a little luck!</message>
    <message key="quest137Title">Warmth in Every Home</message>
    <message key="quest137Description">A fireplace is warm and cozy, not to mention a testament to your affluence. Just imagine those long winter evenings in your favorite armchair, wrapped in a warm blanket!</message>
    <message key="quest137Task2Title">Install a fireplace</message>
    <message key="quest138Title">Hard worker</message>
    <message key="quest138Description">No matter the time or the weather, you're always ready to work. You are a real inspiration to others. You should be proud!</message>
    <message key="quest139Title">Gatherer</message>
    <message key="quest139Description">Doing work and completing various actions in the game may give you various materials to use in the workshop.
Let's stockpile some materials, since they will be useful later.</message>
    <message key="quest140Title">Plush Joy</message>
    <message key="quest140Description">It's easy to make gifts with your bare hands when you have a workshop. Imagine the joy of visiting someone's home and seeing their apartment decorated with the gifts you've made!</message>
    <message key="quest140Task2Title">Give the bear to someone as a present</message>
    <message key="quest141Title">In Search of Happiness</message>
    <message key="quest141Description">Happiness… What does it mean to you? Do you enjoy doing nice things for others? Or does something else make you happy?</message>
    <message key="quest142Title">Hugs and Kisses</message>
    <message key="quest142Description">A friendly embrace, a friendly kiss… Perhaps it's more than 'just friends'? Could this be the love of your life?</message>
    <message key="quest143Title">Home Technology</message>
    <message key="quest143Description">Not only will home technology enhance your apartment, it will also make it more functional. Watching entertaining TV shows or listening to your favorite music will diversify your downtime.</message>
    <message key="quest143Task1Title">Buy a TV</message>
    <message key="quest143Task2Title">Buy a musical center</message>
    <message key="quest143Task3Title">Buy 2 speakers</message>
    <message key="quest151Title">A Feathery Wonder</message>
    <message key="quest151Description">Any good pillow fight starts with a good pillow. Sometimes feathers will fly out of pillows, and you can use them in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest152Title">Snappy Dresser</message>
    <message key="quest152Description">Wearing the very latest trends is the goal of every fashionista, is it not?</message>
    <message key="quest153Title">Jingle of Coins</message>
    <message key="quest153Description">Cleaning your neighbors' apartments can be doubly lucrative when you chance upon a lucky coin. Happiness, here we come!</message>
    <message key="quest154Title">Have Your Fun</message>
    <message key="quest154Description">Work done, have your fun. It's time for some misbehaving!</message>
    <message key="quest155Title">Body and Soul</message>
    <message key="quest155Description">The Club and Cafe are the most popular and fun places to have a good time. Why don't you drop by right now?</message>
    <message key="quest156Title">Fortunate Wheel</message>
    <message key="quest156Description">Fortune's Wheel is a game of chance where you can win it all with just a spin!</message>
    <message key="quest157Title">Energy Overload</message>
    <message key="quest157Description">This task is fully dedicated to energy. You need to work in the workshop and then look to restoring your own reserves of energy.</message>
    <message key="quest158Title">Holiday for the Soul</message>
    <message key="quest158Description">The Cafe sells the tastiest pastries and their pizza is out of this world! And the coffee… the aroma will drive you crazy!</message>
    <message key="quest159Title">Don't Worry, Be Happy!</message>
    <message key="quest159Description">Want to be happy? Go right ahead!</message>
    <message key="quest160Title">Useful Finds</message>
    <message key="quest160Description">One man's trash is another man's treasure! Lots of handy things can be found while cleaning up.</message>
    <message key="quest161Title">Important Guests</message>
    <message key="quest161Description">Now is the perfect time to throw a party. Make sure you invite lots of guests and get ready to have a good time!</message>
    <message key="quest162Title">Boom!</message>
    <message key="quest162Description">Some call it fun, others call it bad behavior. Either way, planting paint bombs and watching people sit on them is loads of fun!</message>
    <message key="quest165Title">Care</message>
    <message key="quest165Description">Giving people warmth and care is the true purpose of humanity. After all, if we don't support one another with kind words, care and affection, nothing good can possibly come of us!</message>
    <message key="quest166Title">Maze</message>
    <message key="quest166Description">There's no such thing as too many rooms, as long as you don't get lost in the maze of sofas, chairs, beds and other things.</message>
    <message key="quest167Title">Craftsmanship</message>
    <message key="quest167Description">The store sells lots of quality items. But you can make plenty of quality items yourself in the Workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest168Title">Flower Marathon</message>
    <message key="quest168Description">It would be nice to assemble a complete collection of table vases.</message>
    <message key="quest169Title">A Healthy Diet</message>
    <message key="quest169Description">What's cold to the touch, but always ready to give up everything it has? A refrigerator! It is the soul of your kitchen, the storehouse of the tasty treats you love.</message>
    <message key="quest170Title">Art</message>
    <message key="quest170Description">A drab wallpaper gets old fast, but that's easy to fix! Simply go to the gift and joke store, buy a few spray paint cans and draw some kickass graffiti right on the wall!</message>
    <message key="quest171Title">Self Decor</message>
    <message key="quest171Description">You've got a brilliant decorative idea. And the best place to implement your plans is the workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest172Title">Spin the Wheel!</message>
    <message key="quest172Description">Go and play, and may luck smile upon you!</message>
    <message key="quest173Title">Capital</message>
    <message key="quest173Description">Keeping all your savings in a cabinet isn't the best way of saving your coins. Why don't you craft a money box in the Workshop to keep your funds from being needlessly wasted?</message>
    <message key="quest174Title">Scoundrel</message>
    <message key="quest174Description">There are always tricks and pranks in your arsenal to entertain others. Just don't show your glee in public!</message>
    <message key="quest175Title">Friendly Assistance</message>
    <message key="quest175Description">After a wild party at your neighbor's apartment, there are heaps of garbage piled up. However, even in the midst of all the scattered trash, you can sometimes find valuable things.</message>
    <message key="quest176Title">Favorite Garden</message>
    <message key="quest176Description">How pleasant it is to spend time in the shade of a tree in the garden! It's a pity these moments only come after long and hard work.</message>
    <message key="quest177Title">Our Street</message>
    <message key="quest177Description">Our street is once again overflowing with garbage, which means you have yet another mountain to climb in your quest for cleanliness. But hey - it's not the first time nor will it be the last.</message>
    <message key="quest178Title">In Reserve</message>
    <message key="quest178Description">You planned to accomplish a lot more today, but it's getting late and you're running on fumes. You wish you could spend the rest of the evening doing something you love.
Fortunately, you can craft something to restore your strength and energy.</message>
    <message key="quest179Title">From Flower to Flower</message>
    <message key="quest179Description">You made a wager with friends that you can catch a collection of butterflies. The more you catch, the higher the chance you'll win the wager.</message>
    <message key="quest180Title">Victory March</message>
    <message key="quest180Description">No time to relax, new victories are ahead! A pillow fight victory may not mean much to some, but to you, every hard-fought win means something.</message>
    <message key="quest181Title">Candlelight</message>
    <message key="quest181Description">Place candles in a room and light them. Don't rush; take your time. Now turn off the light and relish the gentle, silent darkness. Oh, where are those candles?</message>
    <message key="quest181Task2Title">Place candles in one of the rooms</message>
    <message key="quest182Title">Chips for Luck</message>
    <message key="quest182Description">Luck is a fickle thing. Today it's on your side, tomorrow it abandons you. But don't fret; each attempt might make you rich!</message>
    <message key="quest183Title">Photographic Memento</message>
    <message key="quest183Description">It's good that you have so many rooms. That means you can put all your favorite photos where everyone can easily see them.</message>
    <message key="quest184Title">Tomfoolery</message>
    <message key="quest184Description">Pranks are loads of fun, especially when two people prank one another. So, no reason to deprive yourself and others of quality entertainment, yes?</message>
    <message key="quest185Title">A Bit Crafty</message>
    <message key="quest185Description">You should make an effort to craft something often, to keep your skills. However, to craft valuable things, you will need a good supply of materials.</message>
    <message key="quest186Title">Make Way for the Kids</message>
    <message key="quest186Description">Wherever you turn, people are shouting, "Make way for the kids!" But where are the kids going? To the Club, of course!</message>
    <message key="quest187Title">Laughter and Tears</message>
    <message key="quest187Description">We're all human, and we express emotions in different ways. It's really just natural!</message>
    <message key="quest188Title">Vases to Order</message>
    <message key="quest188Description">Your buddy has opened up a small store in the center of town and has asked you to craft a batch of decorative vases to sell there. You've been promised a generous payment.</message>
    <message key="quest189Title">Dive Right In!</message>
    <message key="quest189Description">People are always dropping by unannounced! A good host always has something for their guests. Well, are you a good host?</message>
    <message key="quest190Title">Construction Materials</message>
    <message key="quest190Description">We are building a better future!</message>
    <message key="quest191Title">Everything will be alright</message>
    <message key="quest191Description">When it rains, it pours! But soon the sun will shine again! Every cloud has a silver lining :).</message>
    <message key="quest192Title">Flower Paradise</message>
    <message key="quest192Description">They say flowers create an incredible atmosphere of comfort and freshness in the home. Let's test that theory.</message>
    <message key="quest192Task2Title">Decorate one of the rooms with lilies</message>
    <message key="quest193Title">Swords Drawn</message>
    <message key="quest193Description">Real weapons can make for fine home decor. Now you just need to obtain some and arrange them in one of the rooms of your apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest193Task2Title">Hang sabers in one of the rooms</message>
    <message key="quest194Title">All That Noise</message>
    <message key="quest194Description">Your neighbors don't even suspect the surprise you're preparing for them. They think you've dropped by to help them with cleaning, but in reality…</message>
    <message key="quest195Title">Operating Expenses</message>
    <message key="quest195Description">That's what you get for inviting guests over. Not only is there a mountain of trash to clean up, the scoundrels even managed to break some of your high-tech gadgets!</message>
    <message key="quest196Title">Everything Gets Used</message>
    <message key="quest196Description">Very soon you might be loaded with orders, so you should save up materials for future jobs.</message>
    <message key="quest197Title">About Nutrition</message>
    <message key="quest197Description">When you're tired of eating at home, you head to the cafe. But when you've been eating there ten days in a row, your thoughts shift back to your dear, sweet home fridge.</message>
    <message key="quest198Title">Pests</message>
    <message key="quest198Description">Have you heard? Everybody's favorite garden has been ravaged by pests. They've overrun the entire garden! We must get rid of them right away.</message>
    <message key="quest199Title">Good Move</message>
    <message key="quest199Description">Every time you claim your prize, you're already thinking about your next win. And about how to spend all this wealth.</message>
    <message key="quest200Title">Order No. 1</message>
    <message key="quest200Description">This order is for table vases with a yellow flower. You will need to make three vases to complete this order. You'll make a decent chunk of change for the order, so get to work.</message>
    <message key="quest201Title">Order No. 2</message>
    <message key="quest201Description">This order is for table vases with an orange flower. You will need to make three vases to complete this order. You'll make a decent chunk of change for the order, so get to work.</message>
    <message key="quest202Title">Order No. 3</message>
    <message key="quest202Description">This order is for table vases with a pink flower. You will need to make three vases to complete this order. You'll make a decent chunk of change for the order, so get to work.</message>
    <message key="quest203Title">Sweet Madness</message>
    <message key="quest203Description">Today the Cafe is hosting a pie throwing tournament. It'll be super fun, and you should definitely participate.</message>
    <message key="quest204Title">Feathering</message>
    <message key="quest204Description">Pillow feathers are a key material for many items that can be crafted in the workshop. You need to keep refilling your supply of this material.</message>
    <message key="quest205Title">Capital</message>
    <message key="quest205Description">It would be nice to save up for the future. You never know what life may throw your way!</message>
    <message key="quest206Title">In Search of Provisions</message>
    <message key="quest206Description">When you're hungry, the Cafe can satisfy any craving! Good thing you know the way!</message>
    <message key="quest207Title">Creative</message>
    <message key="quest207Description">Let your imagination soar! Be creative! Invent and realize your dreams! It's all in your hands!</message>
    <message key="quest208Title">Garbage Watch</message>
    <message key="quest208Description">The citizens jokingly call street work "garbage watch." But whatever you call it, it sure pays well.</message>
    <message key="quest209Title">Interior Design</message>
    <message key="quest209Description">By crafting pretty furniture in the workshop and placing it in your apartment, you can make your home a lot more cozy.</message>
    <message key="quest210Title">The Custodian</message>
    <message key="quest210Description">Why is it that when large groups of people gather, they tend to leave mountains of trash behind? It's a good thing there are many thoughtful citizens like you to clean up the mess!</message>
    <message key="quest211Title">Give Me Wings!</message>
    <message key="quest211Description">Oh, why can't people fly like butterflies? We could learn plenty from those lovely creatures.</message>
    <message key="quest212Title">Thinking of Yourself and Others</message>
    <message key="quest212Description">Giving presents is always fun, but receiving presents is even better! Especially that special gift you give to yourself.</message>
    <message key="quest213Title">Weight in Gold</message>
    <message key="quest213Description">You've won gold coins playing Fortune's Wheel before, haven't you? Then surely you can win again!</message>
    <message key="quest214Title">Old Photographs</message>
    <message key="quest214Description">You have a new project with your friends — collecting old photographs and crafting a lovely photo album. You'd better get going on your part.</message>
    <message key="quest215Title">One More Chance</message>
    <message key="quest215Description">Every chip means another ticket to play the Wheel. And that's another chance to challenge fate and test your fortune!</message>
    <message key="quest216Title">Bustle in the Garden</message>
    <message key="quest216Description">Warm climate and good weather are welcomed not only by you, but by all inhabitants of the Garden. Including beetles.</message>
    <message key="quest217Title">Pour, Pour, Pour!</message>
    <message key="quest217Description">Flowers need lots of attention; only then do they show off their beauty. Don't let them wither!</message>
    <message key="quest218Title">Victory!</message>
    <message key="quest218Description">For some reason, every time you meet your friends a pillow fight breaks out. And hey... why not?</message>
    <message key="quest219Title">Party Boom</message>
    <message key="quest219Description">Preparing a party? Expecting guests? Then it's your responsibility to make sure the party explodes with fun. Literally!</message>
    <message key="quest220Title">Flower Buds</message>
    <message key="quest220Description">Working in the garden is both useful and fun. Not to mention this is the place to collect all sorts of materials for the workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest221Title">Helpful in Many Ways</message>
    <message key="quest221Description">There is a lot of work to be done in the Street! Plus, you'll collect plenty of bottles for your workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest222Title">Light Up Our Lives</message>
    <message key="quest222Description">To live a bright life, you need bright colors. Make your dull daily routine more interesting!</message>
    <message key="quest223Title">Skilled Hands</message>
    <message key="quest223Description">You are an excellent craftsman. Anyone would be proud to present your work to a best friend or loved one. And you make it all out of random materials found all over town!</message>
    <message key="quest224Title">An Invitation</message>
    <message key="quest224Description">Is your apartment fully furnished? Then it's time to invite all your friends to a house warming party. Just be sure the new furniture doesn't get soiled or broken :)</message>
    <message key="quest225Title">Test of the Feather</message>
    <message key="quest225Description">Pillow feathers can have many uses. Some use them to decorate ancient Indian masks, while others dip the tip of a feather in ink and write poetry.</message>
    <message key="quest226Title">No More Buzzing!</message>
    <message key="quest226Description">These mosquitoes are unbearable! We must find a way to get rid of them. A can of bug spray would be just what the doctor ordered.</message>
    <message key="quest227Title">The Game Is Worth the Candle</message>
    <message key="quest227Description">The game is worth the candle… But where's the game? And where are the candles???</message>
    <message key="quest228Title">Litterers</message>
    <message key="quest228Description">What happened here? Clearly the kids had a little too much fun with yet another pillow fighting contest and forgot to clean up after themselves.</message>
    <message key="quest229Title">Scratch My Back, I Scratch Yours</message>
    <message key="quest229Description">It's good when your fridge is stocked with food. But what if it's empty? That's right - it's time to pay someone a visit!</message>
    <message key="quest230Title">Wrapping Paper</message>
    <message key="quest230Description">No, no, these aren't just some used candy wrappers discarded by kids right on the street. This is actual wrapping paper, which adds a real nice touch to the things you craft in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest231Title">From Start to Finish</message>
    <message key="quest231Description">It's not like you to quit on a project half way through. When you start something, you make sure to see it through.</message>
    <message key="quest232Title">Big Spender</message>
    <message key="quest232Description">It's fun to make money, but it's even more fun to spend it. It's time to indulge in a little retail therapy!</message>
    <message key="quest233Title">Like a Castle</message>
    <message key="quest233Description">You have transformed your drab apartment into a castle! A true testament to good taste!</message>
    <message key="quest234Title">My Victories</message>
    <message key="quest234Description">Nothing ventured, nothing gained. A little bit of luck goes a long way.</message>
    <message key="quest235Title">Make It!</message>
    <message key="quest235Description">Just make it! Make what, exactly? That's up to you to decide. Whether a lovely flower vase or some other decorative piece - it's all in your hands.</message>
    <message key="quest236Title">Blacksmith</message>
    <message key="quest236Description">In the times gone by weapons were only crafted by true blacksmiths, but those times are ancient history. These days, weapons are nothing more but an interior decoration.</message>
    <message key="quest237Title">My Treat!</message>
    <message key="quest237Description">There are many interesting conversations to be had in the Cafe, but if you really want to unwind there's no better place than the Club.</message>
    <message key="quest238Title">Wings and Feathers</message>
    <message key="quest238Description">Catching butterflies and collecting feathers is your objective for today. And if you can't get it all done today, fear not - there's always tomorrow.</message>
    <message key="quest239Title">Coffee Machine</message>
    <message key="quest239Description">Coffee beans can be made into a strong and refreshing drink that will charge you up for the rest of the day.</message>
    <message key="quest240Title">Proper Lighting</message>
    <message key="quest240Description">Miniature candles will make a fine decoration for any room. All you need to do is obtain the required amounts of wax and start crafting.</message>
    <message key="quest241Title">Stains</message>
    <message key="quest241Description">The stain from a paint bomb is easy enough to clean, but the shock of the explosion lingers on.</message>
    <message key="quest242Title">Time for Victories</message>
    <message key="quest242Description">The more levels you gain, the more money you get from Fortune's Wheel. And that means more time left for fun activities with your friends and for hobbies.</message>
    <message key="quest243Title">Beautifying</message>
    <message key="quest243Description">Beauty is in the eye of the beholder. Some find beauty in graffiti tags on the walls, while others need only gaze into the starry sky…</message>
    <message key="quest244Title">Spring Cleaning</message>
    <message key="quest244Description">It doesn't matter which season it is. Spring cleaning means one thing and one thing only: lots and lots of hard work to achieve the desired result.</message>
    <message key="quest245Title">Flea Market</message>
    <message key="quest245Description">It's time to get rid of that old furniture and replace the with the latest styles!</message>
    <message key="quest245Task1Title">Sell old furniture</message>
    <message key="quest246Title">Instruction</message>
    <message key="quest246Description">Be generous with love, and happiness will always find you.</message>
    <message key="quest247Title">Home and Hearth</message>
    <message key="quest247Description">Nothing beats relaxing in the evening next to your home fireplace. And you don't even need to buy one in a store. In fact, you can craft one in the Workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest247Task2Title">Buy a refrigerator</message>
    <message key="quest248Title">Pleasant Meetings</message>
    <message key="quest248Description">Do you know where best friends prefer to meet? In the Cafe, of course! Either that or they visit each other. That's always an option :)</message>
    <message key="quest249Title">A Terrible Power</message>
    <message key="quest249Description">Some say, "Beauty is a power." If that's true, the Beauty Salon is the place to start. Let's tap some of it for ourselves, shall we?</message>
    <message key="quest250Title">Master Breakers</message>
    <message key="quest250Description">Things don't just break on their own, but breaking them on purpose means lots of repair work. But you can't stay mad at your friends, now can you?</message>
    <message key="quest251Title">Cup of Coffee</message>
    <message key="quest251Description">A strong cup of coffee in the morning will help you to wake up and start your day in good spirits.</message>
    <message key="quest252Title">Storeroom</message>
    <message key="quest252Description">The Workshop storeroom still has plenty of space. And seeing as serious projects require plenty of materials, you should go ahead and stock up.</message>
    <message key="quest253Title">Photo Studio</message>
    <message key="quest253Description">Your workshop looks like a real photo studio, with photos scattered everywhere and shelves bursting with frames, displaying some of life's finest moments.</message>
    <message key="quest254Title">My Weapon, the Pillow</message>
    <message key="quest254Description">A good old-fashioned pillow fight is still the most popular method to settle any heated argument. All the fun of a good fight minus the pain and bruises :)</message>
    <message key="quest255Title">House Party</message>
    <message key="quest255Description">A good party is always something to look forward to. After all, that's when you get to see all your friends and loved ones in one place.</message>
    <message key="quest256Title">Generous Treats</message>
    <message key="quest256Description">It's always nice to buy a treat for someone, whether a good friend or a stranger in the Cafe.</message>
    <message key="quest257Title">Gold Mine</message>
    <message key="quest257Description">It's time to play big! Go for the gold!</message>
    <message key="quest258Title">Gifts</message>
    <message key="quest258Description">You'll be having guests over soon, and there's nothing they'd like more than presents made with your own hands. Let's get to work!</message>
    <message key="quest259Title">More Chores</message>
    <message key="quest259Description">Plenty of work has piled up in the Garden and in the Street. You shouldn't put if off any longer. Besides, the sooner you deal with it, the sooner you'll be able to relax.</message>
    <message key="quest260Title">Frequent Guest</message>
    <message key="quest260Description">Your friends and acquaintances are always glad to have you over for a visit. Let's do it more often!</message>
    <message key="quest261Title">Presents for All</message>
    <message key="quest261Description">When on a shopping spree, don't forget to pick up presents for your friends and loved ones. After all, giving presents just feels good!</message>
    <message key="quest262Title">Club Party</message>
    <message key="quest262Description">An evening at the Club promises to be interesting. The weather isn't good for pleasure walks, but just right for popping into the club and having a blast!</message>
    <message key="quest263Title">Pedestal</message>
    <message key="quest263Description">Only those who are worthy can stand at the victory podium, and there are few more worthy than you!</message>
    <message key="quest264Title">Quarry</message>
    <message key="quest264Description">A quarry is typically used to produce clay. But you don't need all that much of it, so whatever you can dig up in the garden will do.</message>
    <message key="quest265Title">Vases</message>
    <message key="quest265Description">These days, decorative vases are in style. This is why they're in such high demand. Many folks have made it a hobby to craft them.</message>
    <message key="quest266Title">Group Cleaning</message>
    <message key="quest266Description">It's time to tidy up - both in yours and in your friends' apartments. Away with garbage! Cleanliness for every home!</message>
    <message key="quest267Title">Coffee Connoisseur</message>
    <message key="quest267Description">To make strong coffee you need roasted coffee beans. Wouldn't it be fun to drop by the Cafe and unwind with friends over a cup of aromatic coffee? Let's go!</message>
    <message key="quest268Title">Counter Punch</message>
    <message key="quest268Description">While your friends are causing trouble, you can cook up some of your own. A paint bomb will not only be fun for everyone, but teach the pranksters a lesson as well.</message>
    <message key="quest269Title">Colors of Life</message>
    <message key="quest269Description">Paint your life with bright colors! And if there's paint left over, color a friend's life, too :)</message>
    <message key="quest270Title">Findings</message>
    <message key="quest270Description">Wrapping paper is needed to package presents. And if you stick a bow on top, that's even better!</message>
    <message key="quest271Title">Pizzeria</message>
    <message key="quest271Description">No matter what your friends may say, the best pizza is served at the local Cafe.</message>
    <message key="quest272Title">Fireplace Hall</message>
    <message key="quest272Description">With so many rooms at your disposal, you can easily furnish one for a fireplace hall, where you can hold both business meetings and masquerade balls :)</message>
    <message key="quest272Task3Title">Buy a new fireplace</message>
    <message key="quest273Title">A Riddle</message>
    <message key="quest273Description">Wonder how long it would take to burn through 5,000 energy? You'll need to look for the answer the old-fashioned way.</message>
    <message key="quest274Title">Generous Gifts</message>
    <message key="quest274Description">You can tell a lot about someone by their shopping choices. And if you're a generous person who likes bringing joy to others, you'll never want for popularity.</message>
    <message key="quest275Title">One Hundred</message>
    <message key="quest275Description">With so many expected and unexpected expenses, there's no such thing as too much money. And if you spend money gradually, soon enough you'll reach a nice round sum.</message>
    <message key="quest276Title">Light Work</message>
    <message key="quest276Description">As the saying goes, "clever hands make light work." And, as it happens, there's plenty of backlogged work to be done in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest277Title">Impressions</message>
    <message key="quest277Description">Having visited the island of Tropicania, you want to keep coming back again and again. In the meantime, you can enjoy the pictures you took of the tropical landscapes.</message>
    <message key="quest278Title">Task List</message>
    <message key="quest278Description">There's a lot on your plate today: the garden needs tending, there's trash piled up outside, and your neighbors have asked for help tidying up. That should really keep you occupied!</message>
    <message key="quest279Title">Components</message>
    <message key="quest279Description">Certain ingredients for the workshop are easier procured than others. The more valuable the ingredient, the harder it is to procure.</message>
    <message key="quest280Title">Valedictorian</message>
    <message key="quest280Description">Do you feel lucky? Well, do you? Then you'll easily complete this task :)</message>
    <message key="quest281Title">Trinity</message>
    <message key="quest281Description">Forget all superstitions - you simply must buy another room. As for furnishing it, that's your own personal business.</message>
    <message key="quest282Title">Play and Win!</message>
    <message key="quest282Description">The more experienced you become, the more money you can win with the Wheel of Fortune. And with your wealth of experience, there's no better time to play big!</message>
    <message key="quest283Title">Road to Comfort</message>
    <message key="quest283Description">It takes great effort to get to reach the very peak of glory. But once there, a magnificent view opens up on all that you were able to achieve.</message>
    <message key="quest284Title">Friendly Hangouts</message>
    <message key="quest284Description">It's good to have lots of friends! And it's not at all scary when a whole crowd of them suddenly crashes your house. In fact, it's awfully pleasant!</message>
    <message key="quest285Title">Conveyor</message>
    <message key="quest285Description">Whoa, you've got so many materials backed up. It might be enough to construct an actual plane! Let's not waste any time and craft a little something.</message>
    <message key="quest286Title">Neighbors Who Are Friends</message>
    <message key="quest286Description">The citizens of Avataria are truly happy, for all their neighbors are also their friends. And all their friends are their neighbors. After all, it's so easy to visit a friend when he lives right next door.</message>
    <message key="quest287Title">The Iron Rule</message>
    <message key="quest287Description">It's not the first time you've crafted a fireplace in the workshop. The main assembly component is iron, which you can find in the yard while cleaning.</message>
    <message key="quest288Title">It Pays to Be Rested</message>
    <message key="quest288Description">If you want to finish all your tasks on time, you need to be well-rested and fresh. Because if you're sleepy and tired, you won't have the energy for anything.</message>
    <message key="quest289Title">On the Wall</message>
    <message key="quest289Description">What can you decorate an apartment wall with? A beautiful painting or a luxury lamp? How trite and boring!</message>
    <message key="quest290Title">Compile and Spend</message>
    <message key="quest290Description">Why do we save up money? To buy something useful. But have you ever wanted to take a whole bunch of money and spend it just because, without thinking?</message>
    <message key="quest291Title">Rare Wares</message>
    <message key="quest291Description">Do you like a little friendly competition? Then try and gather rare materials before anyone else!</message>
    <message key="quest292Title">Technology, a Powerful Force</message>
    <message key="quest292Description">Want all your friends to know that you're the most tech savvy of them all? You've got to prove your prowess first. Go get that plasma screen and new fridge!</message>
    <message key="quest292Task1Title">Buy plasma TV</message>
    <message key="quest293Title">Surprise</message>
    <message key="quest293Description">It's always great to get a gift from a good friend. Especially when that friend keeps giving and giving!</message>
    <message key="quest294Title">A Change of Image</message>
    <message key="quest294Description">Had enough of your old image? Want to stand out from the crowd? Make yourself a new look! Hairstyle, eyebrows, and maybe something else, too...</message>
    <message key="quest295Title">Stylish Accessories</message>
    <message key="quest295Description">Have you seen those wonderful seashell necklaces in the workshop? Everyone who's been to our wonderful beach should have one!</message>
    <message key="quest296Title">I'm a Model</message>
    <message key="quest296Description">Want to feel like a world-famous star? Head to our Photo Studio. There you can find all kinds of accessories to take you on a trip down Fantasy Lane!</message>
    <message key="quest297Title">Technology Guru</message>
    <message key="quest297Description">Invention is a delicate business, but we know you can do it!</message>
    <message key="quest298Title">Lucky Shot</message>
    <message key="quest298Description">You should be in luck today!</message>
    <message key="quest299Title">Valuable Finds</message>
    <message key="quest299Description">Ah, the surf, the sun… warm places are so wonderful! Let's go to the sunny beach to collect some souvenirs of this great vacation.</message>
    <message key="quest300Title">Call of the Jungle</message>
    <message key="quest300Description">You haven't been to my garden for so long, and now the neighbors have nicknamed the place 'the jungle'! Get to work on those weeds!</message>
    <message key="quest301Title">Total Weeding</message>
    <message key="quest301Description">Looks like that strong wind brought us an unpleasant surprise. Clean up the trash that's scattered in the streets!</message>
    <message key="quest302Title">Work Can't Wait</message>
    <message key="quest302Description">Sometimes life brings us difficult challenges. Like work, for instance. Even when we don't want to do it, we still have to.</message>
    <message key="quest303Title">Big Spender</message>
    <message key="quest303Description">People who don't know how to spend money wisely don't know how to make it, either. Time to spend some money on yourself!</message>
    <message key="quest304Title">Collector of Emotions</message>
    <message key="quest304Description">Life without emotions would be so boring! But keeping emotions to yourself isn't smart. Let's share them with everyone around!</message>
    <message key="quest305Title">Party All Night!</message>
    <message key="quest305Description">Want to spend all night at a noisy party instead of in dream land? Then head to the club. We've got the best cocktails and the wildest parties!</message>
    <message key="quest306Title">Cleanup Champ</message>
    <message key="quest306Description">Did you hear about the neighbor cleanup master class? Well, you're right – why sit around wasting words? Let's get to work instead!</message>
    <message key="quest307Title">Warm Embrace</message>
    <message key="quest307Description">You can always keep warm even if the temperatures outside plummet. By hugging others, of course! Hug your friends to help keep them from freezing!</message>
    <message key="quest308Title">Party-Goer</message>
    <message key="quest308Description">Your friends will have a blast if you throw a party at home! Do everything you can to have a great time!</message>
    <message key="quest309Title">Hunger Pains</message>
    <message key="quest309Description">Everyone loves a bite to eat! It's great to be able to throw open your friend's refrigerator and grab a few bites of sausage.</message>
    <message key="quest310Title">Evil Genius</message>
    <message key="quest310Description">I bet you have a few enemies by now. And a few pranks you want to pull. Just little ones :)</message>
    <message key="quest311Title">Surf's Up!</message>
    <message key="quest311Description">All of your friends are at the beach already, getting ready for a new season of surfing! You don't want to fall behind, do you?</message>
    <message key="quest312Title">Sea Battle</message>
    <message key="quest312Description">All those training sessions paid off! And now you have a good chance of competing in the finals with Avataria's greatest surfing masters!</message>
    <message key="quest313Title">Breaker</message>
    <message key="quest313Description">With your surfing skills, challenging you is a real headache for anyone! Come on, try and catch me!</message>
    <message key="quest314Title">Gifts of the Sea</message>
    <message key="quest314Description">Seashell necklaces are in high demand among Avataria's residents. If only they knew how tough it is to find the necessary materials sometimes!</message>
    <message key="quest315Title">Pearl Divers</message>
    <message key="quest315Description">One of my friends recently bragged to me that he found a whole mountain of pearls in the nearby gulf. Maybe you can find some too?</message>
    <message key="quest316Title">Jewelry Shop</message>
    <message key="quest316Description">Collecting the materials for the necklace wasn't so bad. You really need to be a master to make a masterpiece out of this stuff, though!</message>
    <message key="quest317Title">Crack!</message>
    <message key="quest317Description">Your surfboard has unexpectedly broken, with the competition season already in full swing! Don't waste any time. Let's make a new one right away!</message>
    <message key="quest318Title">On All Fronts</message>
    <message key="quest318Description">Be a lifelong champion!</message>
    <message key="quest319Title">Red or Blue?</message>
    <message key="quest319Description">Which color is the richest and brightest: red or blue? Time to run some experiments in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="quest320Title">Memories</message>
    <message key="quest320Description">What's the best way to remember the greatest moments in life? Capturing them on film, of course!</message>
    <message key="quest321Title">Best Photos</message>
    <message key="quest321Description">Where can you get the best photos? In Avataria's photo studio, where else?</message>
    <message key="quest322Title">Photo Shoot</message>
    <message key="quest322Description">Avataria's photo studio is where you can find gorgeous props and backgrounds and the best technology and lighting. Don't believe me? Let's go and you'll see for yourself!</message>
    <message key="quest323Title">VIP Energy Boost</message>
    <message key="quest323Description">Did you know that you can rest up in the club's VIP room? Well, come on, that's where we're going today!</message>
    <message key="quest324Title">Supplies</message>
    <message key="quest324Description">Basic food reserves are kept at home in your refrigerator, of course. But there are lots of places around where you can get some more food for yourself!</message>
    <message key="quest325Title">Just Dropping By...</message>
    <message key="quest325Description">Just recently your friends visited and made a real mess in your apartment. Time to get back at them!</message>
    <message key="quest326Title">Onward, Faithful Steed!</message>
    <message key="quest326Description">Have you seen those great horse and dragon swings? Riding on them would be lots of fun!</message>
    <message key="quest327Title">Knights and Dragons</message>
    <message key="quest327Description">In the days of the knights, every warrior dreamed of defeating the dragon. And every knight needs a big sword, or at least a saber!</message>
    <message key="fsTitle">Silver Fortune</message>
    <message key="fsDescription">If you get lucky, you can win loads of silver coins. Are you ready to spin Fortune's Wheel?</message>
    <message key="fgTitle">Golden Fortune</message>
    <message key="fgDescription">Winning gold at Fortune's Wheel is much harder than winning silver. But nothing's impossible!</message>
    <message key="fcTitle">Spin-Spin-Spin</message>
    <message key="fcDescription">Every chip you win at Fortune's Wheel is another chance to try your luck. A minor payout, but pleasant nonetheless!</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesTitle">Glasses Collection</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesDescription">By collecting glasses you never have to worry about which accessory matches which piece of clothing. Glasses are always in fashion!</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesBoyTask1">Buy gold frame glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesBoyTask2">Buy glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesBoyTask3">Buy light frame glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesBoyTask4">Buy dark glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesBoyTask5">Buy brown lens glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesGirlTask1">Buy gold-adorned glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesGirlTask2">Buy gold glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesGirlTask3">Buy pink glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesGirlTask4">Buy glasses</message>
    <message key="collectGlassesGirlTask5">Buy purple glasses</message>
    <message key="quest122Title">Sweet Revenge</message>
    <message key="quest122Description">Turns out that not only can pies be eaten, they can also be thrown at people! If someone throws a pie at you, don't fret - it's actually pretty fun! Give it a try!</message>
    <message key="quest123Title">VIP</message>
    <message key="quest123Description">Do you like being the center of attention? Open up new horizons for yourself which only VIP status can grant! Add color to your life!</message>
    <message key="quest123Task1Title">Get and extend your VIP status</message>
    <message key="quest123Comment">Hint: Buy or extend VIP status by clicking on the crown icon in the upper part of the screen.</message>
    <message key="quest124Title">VIP Gift</message>
    <message key="quest124Description">Want to do something nice for someone? Then give them VIP status! Trust me, no gift is more valuable. Give your friends and buddies the best gift in town!</message>
    <message key="quest124Task1Title">Give VIP status to someone</message>
    <message key="quest124Comment">Hint: You can give VIP status to someone by clicking on another player and selecting the appropriate option from the Gifts menu.</message>
    <message key="quest125Title">Party</message>
    <message key="quest125Description">It's time to make new friends. If you throw an outrageous party, it will draw all sorts of wild and fun people!</message>
    <message key="quest126Title">Early Successes</message>
    <message key="quest126Description">Success bring trophies. You can place trophies in your apartment to make others jealous. And now it's time to earn your first trophy!</message>
    <message key="quest126Task1Title">Earn any bronze trophy</message>
    <message key="rewardComment">Hint: Look for the trophy descriptions in the Trophies tab of the Inventory.</message>
    <message key="quest127Title">Appearance</message>
    <message key="quest127Description">Bored with your look? That's easy to fix. Let's start with a new hairstyle!</message>
    <message key="quest127Task1Title">Change your hairstyle</message>
    <message key="quest127Comment">Hint: To change your hairstyle, click on Appearance in the lower part of the screen.</message>
    <message key="quest128Title">Beauty Salon</message>
    <message key="quest128Description">A master stylist can offer a wider selection of hairstyles and other services. Isn't it time you visited the professionals at the Beauty Salon?</message>
    <message key="quest128Task1Title">Change your hairstyle in the beauty salon</message>
    <message key="quest128Task2Title">Change your eyes in the beauty salon</message>
    <message key="quest128Task3Title">Change your lips in the beauty salon</message>
    <message key="quest129Title">With Your Bare Hands</message>
    <message key="quest129Description">Do you like to make things from scratch? That's why you have a workshop with a bunch of blueprints and schematics. You can craft useful items for yourself and to give to friends.</message>
    <message key="quest130Title">Piggy</message>
    <message key="quest130Description">It's easy to make gifts with your own hands when you have a workshop. Imagine the joy of visiting someone's home and seeing that the centerpiece of the apartment is the gift made by you.</message>
    <message key="quest130Task2Title">Give the money box to someone</message>
    <message key="quest132Title">Mailbox</message>
    <message key="quest132Description">Your friends and buddies can send you messages if you have a mailbox. You should buy one and install it in your apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest132Task1Title">Buy a Mailbox</message>
    <message key="quest132Task2Title">Install a mailbox in your apartment</message>
    <message key="quest132Comment">Hint: Look for the mailbox in the Technology tab of the Furniture Store.</message>
    <message key="quest144Title">Holiday Bustle</message>
    <message key="quest144Description">The holidays are approaching, let's clean up in preparation for the celebration!</message>
    <message key="quest144Comment">Hint: To clean up garbage in the Street, click on “Places” and select “Street Cleaner” from the Work tab.</message>
    <message key="quest145Title">Christmas Tree</message>
    <message key="quest145Description">You've been awarded a Christmas tree for completing one of your tasks. Let's put it up!</message>
    <message key="quest145Task1Title">Put up a Christmas tree in the apartment</message>
    <message key="quest163Title">Decorating the Tree</message>
    <message key="quest163Description">Now that the Christmas tree is up, let's decorate!</message>
    <message key="quest163Task1Title">Put a topper on the Christmas tree</message>
    <message key="quest163Task2Title">Hang 5 Christmas toys</message>
    <message key="quest163Comment">Hint: Click on the Christmas tree to decorate it.</message>
    <message key="quest164Title">Christmas Toys</message>
    <message key="quest164Description">By giving someone a Christmas toy, you're spreading joy and true holiday spirit.</message>
    <message key="quest164Task1Title">Give 5 Christmas toys</message>
    <message key="quest164Comment">Hint: To give someone a Christmas toy, click on somebody's Christmas tree and select Give a Toy.</message>
    <message key="quest146Title">Victorious</message>
    <message key="quest146Description">There are many ways to settle a dispute, but the best way is to have a pillow fight.</message>
    <message key="quest146Comment">Hint: A feather may fall out during a pillow fight. Or it may not :)</message>
    <message key="quest147Title">Tough Break</message>
    <message key="quest147Description">Sometimes thing get broken! But not to worry, they are all easily fixed.</message>
    <message key="quest148Title">Second Degree</message>
    <message key="quest148Description">A silver trophy is the second degree of any achievement. Can you earn one?</message>
    <message key="quest148Task1Title">Earn a silver trophy</message>
    <message key="quest149Title">Third Degree</message>
    <message key="quest149Description">A gold trophy is the highest degree of any achievement. Can you earn one?</message>
    <message key="quest149Task1Title">Earn a gold trophy</message>
    <message key="spd1Title">Leprechaun</message>
    <message key="spd1Description">Do you know what leprechauns are? These funny creatures are the main symbol of St. Patrick's Day. And now you can craft a leprechaun statuette in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="spd1Task1Title">Craft a leprechaun statuette</message>
    <message key="spd2Title">St. Patrick's Day</message>
    <message key="spd2Description">The stores have stocked up on new green-tinged clothes for St. Patrick's Day. Don't get left behind, get yourself cool new gear!</message>
    <message key="spd2Task1Title">Buy an item of clothing for St. Patrick's Day</message>
    <message key="spd3Title">The Party's On!</message>
    <message key="spd3Description">Leprechaun, leprechaun, the party's on! Your friends will come to the party soon, and you simply must show them your leprechaun.</message>
    <message key="spd3Task1Title">Place a leprechaun figurine in your apartment</message>
    <message key="spd3Task2Title">Invite your friends to the party</message>
    <message key="foolsDayQuestTitle">April Miracle</message>
    <message key="foolsDayQuestDescription">You can earn 100 gold coins for competing this special quest right now!!! But you'd better hurry, since this quest will soon disappear, and along with it... 100 gold coins!</message>
    <message key="foolsDayQuestTask1Title">Visit the street 25 times
with a 24 hour period</message>
    <message key="easterQuest1Title">Easter is Coming</message>
    <message key="easterQuest1Description">New recipes have appeared in the workshop, which means it's time for you to prepare for the Easter celebration.</message>
    <message key="easterQuest1Task1Title">Craft a green Easter Egg</message>
    <message key="easterQuest1Task2Title">Craft a purple Easter Egg</message>
    <message key="easterQuest1Task3Title">Craft a blue Easter Egg</message>
    <message key="easterQuest1Comment">Hint: Use an Easter Egg recipe in the workshop to craft an egg of either of the three colors.</message>
    <message key="easterQuest2Title">Easter Presents</message>
    <message key="easterQuest2Description">You can't have Easter without presents! Give a present to someone, and you will surely get one in return!</message>
    <message key="easterQuest2Task1Title">Give a purple Easter Egg</message>
    <message key="easterQuest2Comment">Hint: Click on one of your friends, then click on Presents and again on Give a Present.</message>
    <message key="victoryQuest1Title">Victory Day!</message>
    <message key="victoryQuest1Description">It happened such a long time ago... May 9, 1945... Do you remember about this day?</message>
    <message key="victoryQuest1Task1Title">Make a St George's ribbon</message>
    <message key="victoryQuest1Task2Title">Draw a Victory Day graffiti</message>
    <message key="victoryQuest1Comment">Hint: You can buy graffiti in the gift and joke store. You can make a St. George's ribbon in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest1Title">Wigwam</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest1Description">Fabric from Tropicania is finer and more durable than the local kind. And that means the items crafted from it are higher in quality.</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest1Task1Title">Craft a wigwam</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest1Comment">Hint: Linen and cotton fabrics can be obtained in the Tropicania game. Then, after building an airdrome there, the fabric can be sent to yourself.</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest2Title">Canoe</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest2Description">Redwood native to Tropicania can be used to craft a real canoe. It is certain to look smashing in your home, though it probably won't get much use, except maybe in the Hot Tub :)</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest2Task1Title">Craft a canoe</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest2Comment">Hint: Redwood can be obtained in the Tropicania game. Then, after building an airdrome there, you can send the wood to yourself.</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest3Title">The Collector</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest3Description">Many ancient artifacts can be found traveling through Tropicania.</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest3Task1Title">Complete your first totem collection</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest3Task2Title">Complete your second totem collection</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest3Task3Title">Complete your third totem collection</message>
    <message key="tropicQuest3Comment">Hint: Totems can be obtained in the Tropicania game. Then, after building an airdrome there, you can send them to yourself.</message>
    <message key="questNY1Title">Christmas!</message>
    <message key="questNY1Description">Christmas is around the corner, and everybody's rushing to the stores to buy presents for their friends and loved ones. So, how about some holiday shopping?</message>
    <message key="questNY1Task1Title">Buy Christmas presents</message>
    <message key="questNY1Task2Title">Send Christmas presents to friends</message>
    <message key="questNY1Comment">Hint: You'll find boxes with presents in the Christmas tab of the shop of gifts and jokes.</message>
    <message key="questNY2Title">Snow Sphere</message>
    <message key="questNY2Description">Not everybody is capable of crafting such a trinket! But those who can handle the job will revel in the beauty made with their own hands.</message>
    <message key="questNY2Task1Title">Craft a snow sphere</message>
    <message key="questNY2Task2Title">Place the sphere in your apartment</message>
    <message key="questNY2Comment">Hint: You can craft this item in the workshop. Click on the toolbox icon to go to the workshop.</message>
    <message key="questNY3Title">Gingerbread</message>
    <message key="questNY3Description">You think it's easy to make a gingerbread man, especially one that's human-sized? It takes lots of time and effort to bake such a culinary masterpiece, but believe me when I say it's worth it!</message>
    <message key="questNY3Task1Title">Bake a gingerbread man</message>
    <message key="questNY3Task2Title">Place the gingerbread man in the apartment</message>
    <message key="questNY3Comment">Hint: You can craft this item in the workshop. Click on the toolbox icon to go to the workshop.</message>
    <message key="questNY4Title">Snowmen</message>
    <message key="questNY4Description">Let's make a snowman, or better yet - two of them. A snowman and his girlfriend - a snowwoman!</message>
    <message key="questNY4Task1Title">Make a snowman</message>
    <message key="questNY4Task2Title">Make a snowwoman</message>
    <message key="questNY4Comment">Hint: Snowmen are made in the workshop. You can use this recipe to randomly receive a decorative snowman or snowwoman.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest1Title">Valentine's Day Cards</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest1Description">Few things are more pleasant than getting a Valentine's Day card. And it doesn't even matter who from, whether an old friend or a charming stranger. On this special day, love knows no bounds!</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest1Task1Title">Get Valentine's Day cards</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest1Comment">Hint: Your friends can send you a Valentine's Day card. For them to do so, you must go to the workshop, find a Valentine's Day card and click Request.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest2Title">Love Balloon</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest2Description">Want to profess your love to someone or simply give them a nice gift? In honor of Valentine's Day, you'll find something special in the workshop!</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest2Task1Title">Craft a LOVE balloon</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest2Comment">Hint: The balloon can be crafted in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest3Title">About Love...</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest3Description">What do we know about love? Not much at all... But we're constantly aspiring to experience everything that this deep emotion has to offer, as well as share our own affection with those dear to us.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest3Task1Title">Get love</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest3Comment">Hint: You can get love by hugging and kissing other avatars.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest4Title">Sweet Kiss</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest4Description">What kind of a holiday is it without sweets? Your friends have been waiting for you to bring them a treat for tea time, and you already know what you'll be bringing.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest4Task1Title">Give a box of candy</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest4Comment">Hint: You'll find the heart-shaped box of candy in the Gifts and Jokes shop.</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest5Title">Hanging Out with Friends</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest5Description">Your friends and you have decided to celebrate this Valentine's Day at the cafe. And we all know how much fun that can be!</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest5Task2Title">Hug someone at the cafe</message>
    <message key="valdayQuest5Task3Title">Hurl a cake at someone at the cafe</message>
    <message key="hbCafeLocationTitle">to the cafe</message>
    <message key="hbClubLocationTitle">to the club</message>
    <message key="hbParkLocationTitle">to the park</message>
    <message key="hbPublicLocationsTitle">locations</message>
    <message key="hbWorkLocationsTitle">work</message>
    <message key="hbClothesShopTitle">clothing store</message>
    <message key="hbFurnitureShopTitle">furniture store</message>
    <message key="hbJokeAndPresentShopTitle">prank shop</message>
    <message key="hbMyinventory">my inventory</message>
    <message key="hbAchievements">trophies</message>
    <message key="hbCraft">to the workshop</message>
    <message key="hbApartment">buy a room</message>
    <message key="hbMngApartment">my apartment</message>
    <message key="hbBeautySalonTitle">to the beauty salon</message>
    <message key="hbAvatarApearance">my appearance</message>
    <message key="hbEventsTitle">create an event</message>
    <message key="hbGardenWorkTitle">work in the garden</message>
    <message key="hbGarbageWorkTitle">work in the yard</message>
    <message key="hbFortuneWorkTitle">wheel of fortune</message>
    <message key="hbBeachLocationTitle">beach</message>
    <message key="hbPhotosalonLocationTitle">photo studio</message>
    <message key="gdBugTitle">Squash beetles</message>
    <message key="gdBtfTitle">Catch butterfly</message>
    <message key="gdFlwTitle">Water flowers</message>
    <message key="gdInsTitle">Spray plants</message>
    <message key="pickGarbage">Clean up trash in the yard</message>
    <message key="pickGarbageComment">Hint: Click on Locations, then go to the Work tab. Select Janitor from the list of jobs.</message>
    <message key="doneGarbageWorkSession">Complete all the work in the yard</message>
    <message key="gwsComment">Hint: You must clean up all the trash before the end of your shift. If some of the trash cannot be seen or cleaned up, go into the location once more.</message>
    <message key="doneGardenWorkSession">Complete all the work in the garden</message>
    <message key="gdwsComment">Hint: You must complete all the jobs before the end of your shift.</message>
    <message key="createGarbageWorkSession">Start a new work shift in the yard</message>
    <message key="cgwsComment">Hint: Only visits during each new work shift are credited. Work shifts change every 30 minutes.</message>
    <message key="createGardenWorkSession">Start a new work shift in the garden</message>
    <message key="cgdwsComment">Hint: Only visits during each new work shift are credited. Work shifts change every 60 minutes.</message>
    <message key="cwsCommonComment">Hint: Only visits during each new work shift are credited.</message>
    <message key="kissAction">Kiss someone</message>
    <message key="hugAction">Hug someone</message>
    <message key="kickAction">Kick someone</message>
    <message key="slapAction">Slap someone</message>
    <message key="giftPresent">Give a gift to someone</message>
    <message key="winPillowBattle">Win a pillow fight</message>
    <message key="throwCake">Throw a pie at someone</message>
    <message key="wipeCake">Wash up from pie remains</message>
    <message key="addBuddy">Make new friends</message>
    <message key="friendsHelp">Clean up your neighbors' trash</message>
    <message key="friendsHelpComment">Hint: All your neighbors are displayed in the lower part of the screen.</message>
    <message key="giftCoctail">Treat someone at the club to a cocktail</message>
    <message key="giftCoctailComment">Hint: Click on one of the players at the club and select Treat.</message>
    <message key="giftSweets">Treat someone at the cafe</message>
    <message key="giftSweetsComment">Hint: Click on one of the players at the cafe and select Treat.</message>
    <message key="giftSomeone">Treat someone at the club or the cafe</message>
    <message key="refrigerateMe">Eat something from your fridge</message>
    <message key="treatTheirs">Treat someone from your fridge</message>
    <message key="treatMe">Eat from someone else's fridge</message>
    <message key="brokeFurniture">Break an object at someone's place</message>
    <message key="repairFurniture">Fix a broken object belonging to you</message>
    <message key="createEvent">Create a new event</message>
    <message key="createEventComment">Hint: To create an event, click on Locations to the left, then open the Events tab. Then select Create an Event below.</message>
    <message key="paintGraffiti">Write graffiti</message>
    <message key="eraseGraffiti">Erase graffiti in your apartment</message>
    <message key="winBeachRace">Win the surf competition</message>
    <message key="makePhoto">Take a picture in the photo studio</message>
    <message key="restoreEnergyInVip">Recharge in the club VIP room</message>
    <message key="sitOnHorse">Take a great ride on the swings</message>
    <message key="collectBow">Find bows while cleaning the yard</message>
    <message key="collectPhial">Find a jar</message>
    <message key="collectBigPhial">Find a large jar</message>
    <message key="collectClay">Collect lumps of clay in the garden</message>
    <message key="collectWater">Find drops of water in the garden</message>
    <message key="collectCoins">Find lucky coins</message>
    <message key="collectFeather">Collect feathers</message>
    <message key="collectWick">Get a fuse</message>
    <message key="collectIron">Collect pieces of iron</message>
    <message key="collectWood">Collect pieces of wood</message>
    <message key="collectPhotos">Collect photographs</message>
    <message key="collectFlowerBuds">Collect buds</message>
    <message key="collectWrappingPaper">Collect wrapping paper</message>
    <message key="collectSaberHilt">Find a saber hilt</message>
    <message key="collectShell">Collect seashells</message>
    <message key="collectPearl">Collect pearls</message>
    <message key="collectComponents">Collect any materials for the workshop</message>
    <message key="collectGenerosity">Receive generosity</message>
    <message key="collectLove">Get love</message>
    <message key="collectHappiness">Receive happiness</message>
    <message key="collectHate">Receive hatred</message>
    <message key="craftCoffeeDrink">Create a caffeinated beverage in the workshop</message>
    <message key="craftEnergyDrink">Create an invigorating beverage in the workshop</message>
    <message key="craftTeddyBear">Craft a teddy bear</message>
    <message key="craftSaber">Craft a saber</message>
    <message key="craftCandel">Craft a candle</message>
    <message key="craftLillies">Craft a bouquet of lilies</message>
    <message key="craftMoneybox">Craft a moneybox</message>
    <message key="craftBomb">Craft paint bombs</message>
    <message key="craftFireplace">Craft a fireplace</message>
    <message key="craftTV">Craft a television</message>
    <message key="craftShellNecklace">Make a seashell necklace</message>
    <message key="craftPearlNecklace">Make a pearl necklace</message>
    <message key="craftFilm">Make some film</message>
    <message key="craftMusCenter">Make a Music Center</message>
    <message key="craftSurfBoard">Make a surfboard</message>
    <message key="craftTableVaseYellow">Craft a vase with a yellow flower</message>
    <message key="craftTableVaseOrange">Craft a vase with an orange flower</message>
    <message key="craftTableVasePink">Craft a vase with a pink flower</message>
    <message key="craftFloorVaseBlue">Craft a blue decorative vase</message>
    <message key="craftFloorVaseRed">Craft a red decorative vase</message>
    <message key="craftPhotoFrameBlue">Craft a blue picture frame</message>
    <message key="craftPhotoFrameRed">Craft a red picture frame</message>
    <message key="craftAnyItem">Craft any item</message>
    <message key="changeClothesRating">Receive image points</message>
    <message key="changeHouseRating">Receive comfort points</message>
    <message key="winChips">Win chips in the Wheel of Fortune</message>
    <message key="winSilver">Win silver in the Wheel of Fortune</message>
    <message key="winGold">Win gold in the Wheel of Fortune</message>
    <message key="buyRoom">Buy a new room</message>
    <message key="buyRoomComment">Hint: To buy another room, click on one of the rooms that doesn't lead outside.</message>
    <message key="questRandomCraftHint">Hint: To get the right color, you might need to craft the item several times.</message>
    <message key="fortuneWin">Win in the Wheel of Fortune</message>
    <message key="fortuneWinComment">Hint: Click on the Chips icon in the lower part of the screen to play Wheel of Fortune.</message>
    <message key="feedYourself">Place an order at the club or the cafe</message>
    <message key="feedYourselfInCafe">Eat at the cafe</message>
    <message key="feedYourselfInClub">Order a cocktail at the club</message>
    <message key="drinkB52InClub">Order some B-52 in the club</message>
    <message key="buyCafeCake">Eat a piece of cake at the cafe</message>
    <message key="buyCafeCoffee">Drink a cup of coffee at the cafe</message>
    <message key="buyCafePizza">Eat a slice of pizza at the cafe</message>
    <message key="spendEnergy">Spend energy</message>
    <message key="spendSilver">Spend silver</message>
    <message key="spendGold">Spend gold</message>
    <message key="danceInClub">Dance at the club</message>
    <message key="danceInStreet">Dance in the street</message>
    <message key="danceInYard">Dance in the square</message>
    <message key="danceInSchool">Dance in the school</message>
    <message key="danceInCafe">Dance at the cafe</message>
    <message key="danceInPark">Dance in the park</message>
    <message key="justDance">Dance</message>
    <message key="plantBomb">Plant a paint bomb</message>
    <message key="plantBombComment">Hint: A paint bomb can be purchased in the prank shop and planted on any chair, armchair or sofa - anywhere one can sit on.</message>
    <message key="roomsCount">Increase the number of rooms in the apartment</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest1Title">Watering</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest1Desc">Plants need watering just like people need feeding. All you need to do is pour some water on them. But don't forget: they need to be watered every day!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest2Title">Beetles</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest2Desc">Look at all the pests! If you don't get rid of them soon, all of the gardening work you've done will be ruined!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest3Title">A Colorful Catch</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest3Desc">A lovely-smelling garden attracts fauna, too. Look at how many different kinds of butterflies are flying around!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest4Title">Pests!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest4Desc">Nature takes care of itself, but sometimes you have to get involved in the process. Some of these bushes need urgent pest control!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest5Title">Fliers and Crawlers</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest5Desc">Who's that flying around the garden? That's right, butterflies. And what's that crawling around in the dirt? Beside you, I mean? Probably some of those nasty garden pests, beetles.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest6Title">Dry Season</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest6Desc">As it gets warmer outside, you need to give more time to your garden plants. Especially when the heat gets high!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest7Title">Learning to be Punctual</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest7Desc">Some things always have to be done at just the right time. For example, if you don't water your garden plants at the right time, the results can be disastrous!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest8Title">Uncatchable</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest8Desc">Catching butterflies isn't that easy. But that just makes it more fun!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest9Title">The Watering Can</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest9Desc">Gardens plant love nourishing, fresh, cool moisture. It helps them grow stronger. Good thing they have you to help them!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest10Title">More Chores</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest10Desc">Ready to get to work? Lots of great jobs are waiting for you in the garden!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest11Title">Soil Work</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest11Desc">Having your own garden is great, but you've got to take good care of it! Let's go get some garden work done!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest12Title">Wonderful Nature</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest12Desc">Such beautiful nature! And so many beautiful flowers in the garden! You should pick a few and put them in a vase!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest13Title">Well-Deserved Rest</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest13Desc">You can't forget about your garden work! But sometimes you should just visit it for a breath of fresh air.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest14Title">Life-Giving Moisture</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest14Desc">Not even a weed can live without water, much less flowers and bushes.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest15Title">Drought</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest15Desc">Look at this weather! It’s great to have the sun out, but it withers the plants. So let’s give them some water!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest16Title">Start stamping!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest16Desc">Lots of beetles have taken up residence in your garden.You need to get rid of them right away.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest17Title">Insect Invasion</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest17Desc">Look at how full of bugs your garden is! But they’re not all good bugs. You’ve got to get rid of the harmful bugs before you can sit around admiring the butterflies.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest18Title">To the Last Drop</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest18Desc">Water is a priceless resource. There’s a reason we teach kids not to waste it! Let’s collect all of the water we can find in the garden.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest19Title">A Butterfly in the Hand</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest19Desc">A butterfly in the hand is better than beetles in the garden!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest20Title">Broken Water Pipe</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest20Desc">Bad news: the water pipe in the garden is busted. They’ve promised they’ll fix it soon, but we should stock up on water, just in case.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest21Title">Hustle and Bustle</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest21Desc">Sitting around chatting in the garden is fun, but to keep the place nice, you need to put a lot of work into it! You need to water the plants and get rid of harmful insects.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest22Title">Good Taste</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest22Desc">These butterflies are so beautiful! Let’s catch some so that we can get a closer look at them! Just be careful: their wings are very fragile!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest23Title">Care</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest23Desc">Plants are very sensitive, delicate things. You have to take constant care of them, watering them, spraying them...</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest24Title">Pests!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest24Desc">Look at all the pests on the garden bushes! We’ve got to spray them fast, or there’ll be nothing left but twigs!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest25Title">Irrigation</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest25Desc">The ancients developed a complicated system of irrigation to water their fields. Now everything is much simpler!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest26Title">Catch it!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest26Desc">Look! What a beautiful butterfly! Let’s catch it!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest27Title">Artificial Rain</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest27Desc">There hasn’t been much rain in a while, so the plants have started to dry out! We’ll need to use watering cans for some artificial precipitation.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest28Title">Constant Care</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest28Desc">You can’t just toss plants in the ground and wait for them to grow up! You have to care for them each and every day. Go water them and clean the pests off of them!</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest29Title">Drop by Drop</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest29Desc">You can fill up a large barrel of water by collecting it one drop at a time.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest30Title">The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest30Desc">Some insects are good, but others are bad. So we catch and admire beautiful butterflies, but we smash beetles.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest31Title">Forgetfulness</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest31Desc">Uh oh....looks like you haven’t sprayed the bushes in a while. A little longer and they might succumb to aphids or other pests. Let’s go fix the situation.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest32Title">Attack of the Beetles</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest32Desc">What’s that climbing around on there? A beetle? Oh, there’s another one! And another! And there, too! We’ve got to get rid of them before they hurt the garden.</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest33Title">Odd-Job Man</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest33Desc">There’s all kinds of work to do in a garden—collecting water, spraying bushes...</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest34Title">Jump Catch</message>
    <message key="grdnType1Quest34Desc">Butterflies can fly pretty high, but if you jump, you can catch the pretty things.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest1Title">With One Stroke</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest1Desc">It's usually a good idea to finish what you start. And never destroy what you've accomplished so far!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest2Title">Clay</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest2Desc">So, what do you know about clay? Right. You can find some in the garden. Then you can use it for whatever you need in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest3Title">Keeping Up Appearances</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest3Desc">Sometimes you don't feel like working, but you've got to work anyway. If you visit the garden often enough, no one will catch on :)</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest4Title">Flora</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest4Desc">Flower buds can be used to make all sorts of wonderful things in the workshop. Let's collect a few.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest5Title">Landscaped Garden</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest5Desc">You have to do a lot of things to keep a garden clean and well-maintained: water the plants, take care of pests, and so on. So, let's get started!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest6Title">Wooden Planks</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest6Desc">Wooden planks can be used to make all sorts of wonderful things in the workshop. Let's collect some.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest7Title">Working in the Garden</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest7Desc">Not everybody knows how tough it is to keep the garden clean, fresh, and beautiful all year round! But I can tell that you do.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest8Title">Helpful Stuff</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest8Desc">The garden doesn't just give you work to do; you can find useful things there, too! Materials for the workshop, for example.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest9Title">Under Control</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest9Desc">You know how to do good work, and you pretty much have everything under control. Keep it up!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest10Title">To Each His Own</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest10Desc">Different citizens of Avataria have different preferences. Some like hosting noisy parties, and other like tending peaceful gardens. To each his own.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest11Title">Pest Control</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest11Desc">We've got some bad news, too: some parasites have gotten into the garden. You've got to get rid of them as soon as possible.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest12Title">Everything's Under Control</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest12Desc">Rested up? Time to get back to it, then! You'll just be hurting yourself if you shirk your work!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest13Title">Required Resources</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest13Desc">You can find some resources lying around in the garden, like pieces of wood. They'll come in handy.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest14Title">Hard Worker</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest14Desc">A good worker is always looking for a job to do and always finishing whatever he starts.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest15Title">Carpenter</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest15Desc">Working with wood is great! But we’ve got nothing to work with. How about we collect a few planks from the garden?</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest16Title">Easygoing</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest16Desc">If you get an early start on your work, finishing it up is no problem. Well, let’s get to it!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest17Title">A Sweet Smell</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest17Desc">Ah, flower buds smell so good! Let’s collect some buds so we can enjoy the smell wherever we go!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest18Title">From Sunup to Sundown</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest18Desc">Sometimes there’s just so much work to do in the garden, you can’t even get one thing done before another thing already needs doing!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest19Title">Jack of All Trades</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest19Desc">The greatest workshop in the world can’t make anything without materials. You always need wooden planks, clay, and flower buds!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest20Title">All’s Well That Ends Well</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest20Desc">“All’s well that ends well,” they say. So let’s make sure we end well! Let’s finish our work in the garden so we can take a nice break.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest21Title">The Art of Sculpture</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest21Desc">We admire beautiful sculptures. But we have no idea how much work goes into them. First of all, you need to find the right material.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest22Title">Work Ethic</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest22Desc">Good gardeners can be found out working day in and day out. That’s why their plants end up smelling so good!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest23Title">A Picnic</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest23Desc">Everyone loves a picnic! Grilled burgers and hot dogs, friendly conversation, kites in the air... But you’ve got to gather some wood and water together first, so you can light the fire and then put it out later!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest24Title">Great!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest24Desc">There’s so much to do. Time to get to work!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest25Title">Just do it!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest25Desc">You’ve already started working in your garden! Just a little more and you’ll be done! Just do it.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest26Title">Right on Schedule</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest26Desc">Work needs to be done not only right but on time, too!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest27Title">Diligence</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest27Desc">People don’t earn a reputation for being diligent unless they’re particularly hardworking! Let’s work hard so people see how diligent we are!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest28Title">Woodcutter</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest28Desc">Time to do some woodworking.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest29Title">Time to mix some clay</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest29Desc">Have you taken a look in the workshop recently? Do you have enough clay in there? Well, let’s get some, then!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest30Title">Healthy, Wealthy, and Wise</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest30Desc">The earlier you start your day in the garden, the sooner you finish. And the sooner you reap the rewards!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest31Title">The Art of Aroma</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest31Desc">You can use flower buds in the Workshop to make lots of items which not only decorate your apartment but make it smell nice, too.</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest32Title">Raw Materials</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest32Desc">Mankind has used clay and wood since ancient times, and they’re still essential materials today. The garden has more than enough of these raw materials, so let’s go find them!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest33Title">Task Complete</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest33Desc">Ah, it’s such a relief once you realize everything that needs doing is done! Don’t procrastinate. Let’s get all of our work done!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest34Title">The Source of Life</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest34Desc">Water is essential for life. And for garden work!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest35Title">From A to Z</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest35Desc">There’s a lot of work to do in the garden, and we’ve got to do it all! Otherwise the garden will get out of control, and we can’t allow that!</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest36Title">Not a Quitter</message>
    <message key="grdnType2Quest36Desc">Always finish what you start. Time to do the last of the garden work!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest1Title">Cleanliness</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest1Desc">Do you like when things are clean? Then you know how to make them that way!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest2Title">Findings</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest2Desc">People litter. It's just a fact of life. But not everything we call "trash" needs to be destroyed right away.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest3Title">Give it 100%!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest3Desc">A yard is only considered clean once absolutely all of the rubbish has been removed from it. So you need to give it 100%!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest4Title">Jars</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest4Desc">Who scattered all this good stuff around here? Oh well. Who cares? Finders keepers! :)</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest5Title">New Changes</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest5Desc">This is unfair. Everyone litters, and you have to clean all of it up! That's not right!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest6Title">Litter, Litter Everywhere</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest6Desc">Hey, you guys! What's going on here? Who's responsible for throwing these candy wrappers all over the place?</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest7Title">Clean As Can Be</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest7Desc">There's always more yard work to be done. And you're always the perfect one for the job. You're better at it than all the rest of us!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest8Title">Scrap Metal</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest8Desc">One man's trash is another man's treasure! For you, this scrap metal is a source of good iron which you can use in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest9Title">My Yard</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest9Desc">Yup. This is your yard. And it's in your best interests to keep it clean and tidy!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest10Title">Wrap It!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest10Desc">Wrapping paper? Of course, you can find some right here. Just needs a bit of searching for.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest11Title">Clean Streets</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest11Desc">Such a tidy person and you leave all this trash in the yard? Go clean things up!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest12Title">Searching for Materials</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest12Desc">It looks like there's not only trash in the yard; there are some helpful materials, too. They'd really come in handy!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest13Title">Playing in the Yard</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest13Desc">The yard's not just there to be cleaned; it's good for recreation, too! No, you don't have to take a rake with you this time...</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest14Title">A Valuable Resource</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest14Desc">What can we put in these big bottles? You should find out. How? Well, go collect them all! :)</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest15Title">Tidying Up</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest15Desc">Your yard is full of trash! We need someone to clean up all this garbage!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest16Title">Metalwork</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest16Desc">Wow, metal! This will come in handy in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest17Title">Mopping Up</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest17Desc">This place is full of trash! Time for spring cleaning!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest18Title">Everything Gets Used</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest18Desc">What do we have here? Bows? Bottles? Paper? We need all of this! I’m taking it!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest19Title">A Responsible Gardener</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest19Desc">Time to get to work in the yard!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest20Title">Bows!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest20Desc">Bows! Bows! Beautiful bows! Let’s grab all of them!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest21Title">Neat Freak</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest21Desc">So, isn’t it much nicer to walk through a nice, clean yard than a trash heap? Let’s clean up the trash and make this yard a little nicer.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest22Title">Cans and Bottles</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest22Desc">Cans and bottles everywhere! Who did this? Why all the litter?! You’ve got to get this cleaned up.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest23Title">Let’s go!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest23Desc">There’s tons of work to do in the yard. Time to get started on it!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest24Title">Wrapping Things Up</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest24Desc">You could really use some wrapping paper. There’s got to be some in the yard!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest25Title">Master of Good Deeds</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest25Desc">Cleaning up trash definitely counts as a good deed. The less trash there is, the cleaner the world is!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest26Title">Careful! There are bottles everywhere!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest26Desc">Whew. I almost stepped on a glass bottle! There’s so many of them in all of this garbage. We’ve got to clean them all up before somebody hurts themselves.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest27Title">Spring Cleaning</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest27Desc">The yard is a total mess! We’ve got to clean things up.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest28Title">Gotta keep everything clean!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest28Desc">Just imagine you’re a great warrior, and the trash is your enemy! Your mission, hero, is to wipe out all of the trash in the yard! Take no prisoners! We do our work quickly and thoroughly.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest29Title">Cleanliness</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest29Desc">Who likes to live in a place full of trash? Nobody. Let’s do some serious cleaning in the yard!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest30Title">Splinters</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest30Desc">Even splinters of wood can come in handy for garden work. Let’s collect the splinters in the yard.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest31Title">Unexpected Guests</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest31Desc">On beautiful days like this, you don’t keep the guests inside. You take them out for a walk around the yard! What if you get some unexpected guests while you’re yard’s a mess like this? You should be prepared!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest32Title">Salvage</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest32Desc">Why do people throw out so much old metal, bottles, and cans? You can make so many useful things out of them!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest33Title">Hop To!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest33Desc">It’s not good to waste time when there’s work to be done. As soon as you get a job, get right to it!</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest34Title">Decoration</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest34Desc">A gift is twice as nice to get when it’s got a nice bow on it. If you collect a few bows, you’ll be able to make a Teddy Bear in the workshop.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest35Title">Treasure Hunter</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest35Desc">If you clean up trash in the yard often enough, you’ll find lots of items useful for garden-related work, like metal and paper.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest36Title">Trash</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest36Desc">Don’t you think our yard has gotten a little too trashy? Let’s clean it up! Maybe we’ll find something useful while we’re at it.</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest37Title">Let’s get to it</message>
    <message key="grbgType1Quest37Desc">Have you just been sitting around? Bored yet? Let’s go do some work in the garden!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest1Title">Luring Lady Luck</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest1Desc">They always say "better luck next time," but this time we need luck on our very first try!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest2Title">Love for the Game</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest2Desc">Show how much you love spinning the wheel for valuable prizes!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest3Title">Killer Wheel</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest3Desc">Everyone's heard about your mastery! But you should always make sure everyone knows you're still the best!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest4Title">Lucky Stiff!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest4Desc">Always keep playing! A good game earns you a great reward!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest5Title">Spinner</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest5Desc">Keep spinning, but don't get dizzy!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest6Title">Lucky Spin</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest6Desc">Smart, talented, and tough. That's you! You'll be a real Wheel of Fortune guru before long ;)</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest7Title">Yo-ho-ho!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest7Desc">You love gold, of course. But it’s not so easy to get! Let’s put on our pirate hats and get some gold with the help of Lady Luck.</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest8Title">Gambling</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest8Desc">I love the thrill of a good game! Pulling the lever and watching your winnings pour out is so much fun!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest9Title">The Spinning Moment</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest9Desc">Give the drum a spin, grab another win!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest10Title">Spin the Wheel</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest10Desc">Spin the wheel to win all kinds of prizes!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest11Title">Fortune’s Favorite</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest11Desc">Wanna know who’s the luckiest person I’ve ever met? You! So what are you waiting for? Spin that wheel!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest12Title">Spinning the Wheel</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest12Desc">Come on baby, show me the money!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest13Title">Slot Champ</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest13Desc">Spin the drum for a big win.</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest14Title">Silver Standard</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest14Desc">Just like gold, you can never have too much silver! Play your way to a big pot of silver!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest15Title">Lady Luck</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest15Desc">How about I boost your luck... while you play some more!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest16Title">Lucky Man</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest16Desc">Luck loves risk takers and big gamblers. And I think you’re both!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest17Title">Gold Hunter</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest17Desc">Size doesn’t matter, they say. But it does when we’re talking about gold! Don’t you agree? You need more gold!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest18Title">Surf's Up!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest18Desc">You’re riding a wave of luck! Spin the wheel and rack up some prizes!</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest19Title">Born to Win</message>
    <message key="frtnQuest19Desc">A natural-born winner like you just can’t lose!</message>
    <message key="may1Quest1Title">Spring is here!</message>
    <message key="may1Quest1Description">And everything’s in bloom! Every participant in Avataria’s spring renovation marathon will get a special prize. Hurry up and join the fun!</message>
    <message key="may1Quest2Title">Souvenir</message>
    <message key="may1Quest2Description">The rulers of Avataria have decided to thank all of the residents with a special souvenir! But to get yours, you need to do a little something for the common good.</message>
    <message key="may1Comment">Hint: You can get this unique gift only during the special event running from April 30 to May 6.</message>
    <message key="quest328Title">Well-Rested Worker</message>
    <message key="quest328Description">Have as much fun as you can! But work comes first :)</message>
    <message key="quest329Title">Handmade</message>
    <message key="quest329Description">Whenever we make something with our own hands, we invest a piece of our soul and emotions in it. That’s why handmade things bring so much joy to us and our guests.</message>
    <message key="quest330Title">Taste of the Sea</message>
    <message key="quest330Description">All meals acquire a special taste at seashore. Let's bring the seaside atmosphere to our kitchen.</message>
    <message key="quest330TaskTitle">Buy items from the Sea Breeze collection</message>
    <message key="quest330Comment">Hint: Only buying different items counts.</message>
    <message key="quest331Title">Open Space</message>
    <message key="quest331Description">We usually know our home way too well, and gradually it becomes too small for us. How amazing is it that in Avataria we can expand our living space without moving anywhere?</message>
    <message key="quest332Title">In the Name of Comfort</message>
    <message key="quest332Description">Home is the place where we spend most of our time. One can experience paradise even in a hut, but it is way better to live in a well-cared-for, comfortable apartment.</message>
    <message key="quest333Title">Start Fresh</message>
    <message key="quest333Description">You are about to start with a new stage in your life. To begin with, we will change the atmosphere in the apartment and pay a visit to the beauty salon.</message>
    <message key="quest334Title">Wind of Change</message>
    <message key="quest334Description">It is time to change and surprise everyone around you. Go to the salon, get a new and exciting look, and emphasize your individuality!</message>
    <message key="quest335Title">Lord of the Manor</message>
    <message key="quest335Description">Just look at your mansion, master! But it seems to me that it’s still not comfortable enough. We need to have more utensils around here.</message>
    <message key="quest336Title">Wardrobe</message>
    <message key="quest336Description">With each level you accumulate more and more clothes. Soon you will have nowhere to store it! Shall we buy more wardrobes?</message>
    <message key="quest336TaskTitle">Buy a wardrobe for the clothes</message>
    <message key="quest337Title">HD and Hi-Fi</message>
    <message key="quest337Description">It is so nice to watch movies on a high-definition TV with high-quality sound!</message>
    <message key="quest338Title">Defend yourself!</message>
    <message key="quest338Description">Defend yourself, sir! What do you mean you don't have a saber? Have you never been to a workshop?</message>
    <message key="quest339Title">Winter is Near</message>
    <message key="quest339Description">It is cold in the winter and sometimes on summer nights. At such a time, it is so nice to relax by the fireplace and admire the bright and luminous flames.</message>
    <message key="quest340Title">Getting Ready</message>
    <message key="quest340Description">Wow, it’s so cool to plant bombs and surprise your friends! You need to go to the workshop and stock up on a few of them.</message>
    <message key="quest341Title">Candlelight</message>
    <message key="quest341Description">Have you noticed how special candlelight is? So soft and shimmering. When the light of candles illuminates the darkness, it gets so cozy inside!</message>
    <message key="quest342Title">Vigor of Body and Spirit</message>
    <message key="quest342Description">Time to cheer up! Let’s have some coffee or another invigorating beverage.</message>
    <message key="quest343Title">Crazy Rhythm of Life</message>
    <message key="quest343Description">To stay informed of all events and new trends, you must not sit still, but constantly keep moving and doing something.</message>
    <message key="quest344Title">Gardener’s Business</message>
    <message key="quest344Description">Cool players should have a cool garden. And a cool garden calls for everyday care.</message>
    <message key="quest345Title">Walking Battery</message>
    <message key="quest345Description">You are one of those who charges everyone around you with energy and positivity. But how can you do this if you are groggy? It's time to cheer up!</message>
    <message key="quest346Title">End of the Shift</message>
    <message key="quest346Description">We love to start with new projects, but it is not always possible to finish them. Let's work a little more and complete all the work in the garden and in the yard.</message>
    <message key="quest347Title">Born to Win</message>
    <message key="quest347Description">Real winners try to win everywhere and in everything. Prove that you are the best at whatever you do!</message>
    <message key="quest348Title">Garage Sale</message>
    <message key="quest348Description">You probably have accumulated a lot of unnecessary things, which all your mezzanines and pantries are full of. It’s always a shame to throw things away. Let's sell them instead - surely someone will be interested.</message>
    <message key="quest348TaskTitle">Sell some unnecessary clothes</message>
    <message key="quest349Title">Take It Out</message>
    <message key="quest349Description">We got a lot of trash in the yard, one can’t even relax properly here - this trash is a real eyesore. You need to take it all out.</message>
    <message key="quest350Title">Collection of Charming Things</message>
    <message key="quest350Description">Shells, pearls and flower buds are so beautiful.  I wish I could surround myself with this beauty. But first, let's collect a few of these charming things.</message>
    <message key="quest351Title">Storeroom</message>
    <message key="quest351Description">Storerooms should never be empty - what if you suddenly needed something when you are in the workshop? We have no time to waste - let’s start searching for useful materials right this minute.</message>
    <message key="quest352Title">Piggy Bank of Emotions</message>
    <message key="quest352Description">No wonder Avataria is a world where dreams come true. In this game, you can get the full range of emotions: love, happiness, hate...</message>
    <message key="quest353Title">King of the Beach</message>
    <message key="quest353Description">How to stand out when at the beach? Naturally, you’ve got to come first in surfing races! Whoever wins becomes the king of the beach. Or the queen.</message>
    <message key="quest354Title">Riding the Wave</message>
    <message key="quest354Description">You can have a lot of fun at the beach, but the most interesting thing to do is, of course, a surfing race.</message>
    <message key="quest355Title">Everything at Once</message>
    <message key="quest355Description">The wheel of fortune awaits us! It is time to get hold of gold, silver and game chips.</message>
    <message key="quest356Title">Money Makes Money</message>
    <message key="quest356Description">They say that fortune is attracted to those who already have it. Let's see if this statement is true!</message>
    <message key="quest357Title">That’s It</message>
    <message key="quest357Description">After a long day of work, it’s so nice to say: “That's it” - and then go and have some rest.</message>
    <message key="quest358Title">Break! Crush!</message>
    <message key="quest358Description">Sometimes if someone ruins your mood, makes you angry, you so want to break or crush something.</message>
    <message key="quest359Title">Music Makes Me Crazy</message>
    <message key="quest359Description">When music makes you crazy, you cannot stand still. It doesn’t matter where you are - in a club, in the street or in a cafe - you just want to dance!</message>
    <message key="quest360Title">Selfie</message>
    <message key="quest360Description">In the Avataria photo studio, you can take a bunch of insane photos, post them on your page and collect a ton of likes! Let's go - friends are waiting for your new photos.</message>
    <message key="quest361Title">Night Watch</message>
    <message key="quest361Description">Sometimes all you want to do when it gets dark is to open the fridge and eat something tasty.</message>
    <message key="quest362Title">To the Fullest</message>
    <message key="quest362Description">Life will be so boring if you don’t let yourself have a good time and have fun!</message>
    <message key="quest363Title">Energy of Dance</message>
    <message key="quest363Description">When you dance for real, when you feel it all the way - you get tired, of course, but then a huge wave of energy engulfs you - just wow!</message>
    <message key="quest364Title">One more!</message>
    <message key="quest364Description">Let’s dance till we drop at the club! Dancing alone is no fun. Treat your friends so that they would help you light up the dance floor.</message>
    <message key="quest365Title">Mischief</message>
    <message key="quest365Description">We are constantly being told that we need to always be calm and quiet. But it’s so boring!</message>
    <message key="quest366Title">Writer</message>
    <message key="quest366Description">People who create graffiti on walls call themselves writers. Feel like a real master of graffiti and paint your friends’ walls!</message>
    <message key="quest367Title">Nice and Loud</message>
    <message key="quest367Description">Let’s make a nice and loud explosion for your friends!</message>
    <message key="quest368Title">Friends’ Pranks</message>
    <message key="quest368Description">Good job, friends! You destroyed everything in the house, covered all the walls with graffiti and threw cake in the face to top things off!</message>
    <message key="quest369Title">Barter</message>
    <message key="quest369Description">If you have a useful thing that you don’t really need, there is definitely someone out there who needs it.</message>
    <message key="quest370Title">Party in the Penthouse</message>
    <message key="quest370Description">You have a huge apartment. You should throw a few parties here that are bound to become legendary.</message>
    <message key="quest371Title">Get Out</message>
    <message key="quest371Description">Your friends got a lot of trash in their apartments. It’s time to tell that trash to get out.</message>
    <message key="quest372Title">Bully</message>
    <message key="quest372Description">Only bullies kick people and slap them in the face.</message>
    <message key="quest373Title">My Treat</message>
    <message key="quest373Description">Treat your guests - they will be so happy, and you are guaranteed to have a great time.</message>
  </locale>
</dictionary>
